[
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the cafe in Coronation Street?",
        "Answer": "Roy's Rolls"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By number of films made which country has the largest film industry?",
        "Answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What song does the main character wake up to every morning in Groundhog Day?",
        "Answer": "I Got You Babe (by Sonny and Cher)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Hasbro 'action figure' got its name from a Robert Mitchum film?",
        "Answer": "G.I. Joe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Star Wars films, which two actors played Obi Wan Kenobi?",
        "Answer": "Alec Guiness and Ewan McGregor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the host of the TV show Q.I.?",
        "Answer": "Stephen Fry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the only character to appear in the first ever Coronation Street who is still in the show as at 2009?",
        "Answer": "Ken Barlow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Anyone Can Fall In Love was a chart hit set to the theme tune of which TV show?",
        "Answer": "EastEnders"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film Black Hawk Down was loosely based on a true incident that took place in 1993 in which country?",
        "Answer": "Somalia - (two helicopters were shot down by rocket propelled grenades)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress, born in 1916, had her legs insured by 20th Century Fox for one million dollars?",
        "Answer": "Betty Grable"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at 2009, what is the last Best Picture Oscar winning film to also win Best Actor and Best Actress Oscars?",
        "Answer": "The Silence Of The Lambs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Velma Kelly and Roxie Hart are the protagonists of which Oscar winning movie?",
        "Answer": "Chicago"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Postman Pat's pet cat?",
        "Answer": "Jess"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1951 film did Fred Astaire appear to dance on the ceiling?",
        "Answer": "Royal Wedding"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Jane opposite Johnny Weissmuller's Tarzan in 1932?",
        "Answer": "Maureen O'Sullivan in Tarzan The Ape Man"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the breed of US detective Columbo's dog?",
        "Answer": "Basset hound"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show Family Guy, what is the name of the Griffins' lecherous neighbour?",
        "Answer": "Glenn Quagmire"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Inspector Morse actor John Thaw was married to which actress at the time of his death in 2001?",
        "Answer": "Sheila Hancock"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In TV show Button Moon, what was the name of Mr Spoon's daughter?",
        "Answer": "Tina Teaspoon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Scottish actress played the TV character Supergran?",
        "Answer": "Gudrun Ure"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In TV show Rentaghost, Sue Nicolls played which character?",
        "Answer": "Nadia Popov"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many boxes are used in the UK version of Deal Or No Deal?",
        "Answer": "22"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the character names of the two hitmen in Pulp Fiction?",
        "Answer": "Vincent Vega and Jules Winnfield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the banker who looked after Jed Clampett's millions in The Beverly Hillbillies?",
        "Answer": "Mr Drysdale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedy duo appeared in the last episode of The Sweeney?",
        "Answer": "Morcambe and Wise"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sicknote was the nickname of a character in which TV series?",
        "Answer": "London's Burning"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which was the first colour film to win aBest Picture Oscar?",
        "Answer": "Gone With The Wind (in 1939)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the Prince Regent in Blackadder The Third?",
        "Answer": "Hugh Laurie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Britain's first black news reader?",
        "Answer": "Trevor MacDonald"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Doctor Who's time box called?",
        "Answer": "The Tardis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor, who died on April 5th 2008, was originally considered for the role of Chief Brody in the 1975 film Jaws?",
        "Answer": "Charlton Heston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the first name of the character Lewis in the TV series of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Robert"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Name all of the seven dwarves in Disney's Snow White And The Seven Dwarfs?",
        "Answer": "Happy, Grumpy, Doc, Sleepy, Sneezy, Dopey and Bashful"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 1999 film 10 Things I Hate About You is based on which Shakespeare play?",
        "Answer": "The Taming Of The Shrew"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first American actor to be nominated for Emmy Awards for portraying the same character on 3 different shows?",
        "Answer": "Kelsey Grammar (Cheers, Frasier and Wings)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the three Bourne films starring Matt Damon what is Bourne's first name?",
        "Answer": "Jason"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the first names of Riggs and Murtaugh in the Lethal Weapon films?",
        "Answer": "Martin (Riggs) and Roger (Murtaugh)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal is at the centre of the film Racing Stripes?",
        "Answer": "A zebra"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the role of Mr Freeze in the film Batman And Robin?",
        "Answer": "Arnold Schwarzenegger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Carry On star died on the stage of the Sunderland Empire in 1976?",
        "Answer": "Sid James"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did the song White Christmas first feature?",
        "Answer": "Holiday Inn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV character has sisters called Daisy and Rose?",
        "Answer": "Hyacinth Bucket"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the first names of the twin girls in Bart's class in The Simpsons?",
        "Answer": "Sherri and Teri"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character has been played by Robert Donat, Kenneth More and Robert Powell in three versions of a British movie?",
        "Answer": "Richard Hannay (in The 39 Steps)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the two voice artists of the cartoon characters Dangermouse and his sidekick Penfold?",
        "Answer": "David Jason and Terry Scott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Stingray, what were the character names of the two female puppets?",
        "Answer": "Marina and Atlanta"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Clint Eastwood film was the catchphrase 'Go ahead, make my day' first used?",
        "Answer": "Sudden Impact"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film featured a parrot called Polynesia?",
        "Answer": "Doctor Doolittle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show The Simpsons, how is the character of Robert Terwilliger normally known?",
        "Answer": "Sideshow Bob"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If Scott is 1, Virgil is 2 and Alan is 3, who are 4 and 5?",
        "Answer": "Gordon and John (Thunderbird pilots)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1976 film Taxi Driver?",
        "Answer": "Martin Scorsese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film Trainspotting is from a novel by which author?",
        "Answer": "Irvine Welsh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Roger Moore's scenes in which Blake Edwards film were filmed during a break from shooting Octopussy?",
        "Answer": "Curse of the Pink Panther"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the character played by Robert de Niro in the 1976 film Taxi Driver?",
        "Answer": "Travis Bickle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1985 film Back To The Future?",
        "Answer": "Robert Zemeckis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who co-starred with her father in the 1959 film Tiger Bay?",
        "Answer": "Hayley Mills"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor was born in 1916 with the real name of Issur Danielovitch Demsky?",
        "Answer": "Kirk Douglas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the sequel to the film American Graffiti?",
        "Answer": "More American Graffiti"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which is the only dwarf that never speaks in Snow White And The Seven Dwarfs?",
        "Answer": "Dopey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous 1927 film is based on the play Day Of Atonement by Samson Raphaelson?",
        "Answer": "The Jazz singer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Roger Moore's scenes in which Blake Edwards film were filmed during a break from shooting Octopussy?",
        "Answer": "Curse of the Pink Panther"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress, model and singer served 18 days in prison for tax evaxion in 1982?",
        "Answer": "Sofia Loren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1976 film Taxi Driver?",
        "Answer": "Martin Scorsese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which other TV soap, other than EastEnders, did Ross Kemp star in?",
        "Answer": "Emmerdale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour are the shorts that Bart Simpson normally wears?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the presenter of the Weakest Link?",
        "Answer": "Anne Robinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Annie Wilkes in the 1990 film 'Misery'?",
        "Answer": "Kathy Bates"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the second James Bond film?",
        "Answer": "From Russia With Love"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the pub in Minder?",
        "Answer": "The Winchester"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the car in the TV series The Dukes of Hazard?",
        "Answer": "The General Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme tune to the TV series The Fall Guy?",
        "Answer": "Lee Majors"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Orson Welles' last movie, in which he voiced a character called Unicron?",
        "Answer": "Transformers: The Movie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the housing estate where the Trotters live in Only Fools And Horses?",
        "Answer": "Nelson Mandela House"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city is the TV series Grey's Anatomy set?",
        "Answer": "Seattle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the movie Aliens, what was the name of the cat?",
        "Answer": "Jones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred in the title role of the film version of J B Priestley's play An Inspector Calls?",
        "Answer": "Alastair Sim"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 2005 Nobel prize-winning English playwright wrote the screenplay for the film The French Lieutenant's Woman?",
        "Answer": "Harold Pinter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which children's television show featured the characters of George, Zippy and Bungle?",
        "Answer": "Rainbow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1969 film was based on Barry Hines novel A Kestrel For A Knave?",
        "Answer": "Kes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Breakfast at Tiffanys', what is the name of Audrey Hepburn's character's cat ?",
        "Answer": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Postman Pat's surname?",
        "Answer": "Clifton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Cannonball Run' what was the name of the super-hero played by Dom DeLuise?",
        "Answer": "Captain Chaos"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you find the character of Caledon 'Cal' Hockley?",
        "Answer": "Titanic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Nathan Detroit in the 1955 film Guys and Dolls?",
        "Answer": "Frank Sinatra"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Charles Fleischer voiced the title character in which 1988 film?",
        "Answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit?"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oscar winning actress played Stella Bridger in the 2003 remake of the Italian Job?",
        "Answer": "Charlize Theron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Billy Costigan in the 2006 Oscar winning film The Departed?",
        "Answer": "Leonardo DiCaprio"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oscar winning screenplay writer also co-wrote the screenplay for the movie Superman 2?",
        "Answer": "Mario Puzo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cast member of The Magnificent Seven had a scene from the film enacted at his wedding during filming?",
        "Answer": "Yul Brynner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the holiday camp in the TV sitcom 'Hi-De-Hi'?",
        "Answer": "Maplins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1959 Alfred Hitchcock film had the tagline 'Its a deadly game of tag and Cary Grant is it!'?",
        "Answer": "North by Northwest"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character played by Ronnie Barker in 'Open All Hours'?",
        "Answer": "Arkwright"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Channel 4 launched?",
        "Answer": "1982"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The theme tune for 'TFI Friday' was taken from which 1960s TV series?",
        "Answer": "Man in a Suitcase"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who provides the voice of Sideshow Bob in 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Kelsey Grammer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "I n the film 'The Great Escape' what were the code names of the 3 tunnels?",
        "Answer": "Tom, Dick and Harry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film character's car had the registration number BMT214A?",
        "Answer": "James Bond (the Aston Martin DB5)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed The 2002 film 'The Pianist'?",
        "Answer": "Roman Polanski"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the baby of Wayne and Waynetta Slob in the Harry Enfield Show?",
        "Answer": "Frogmella"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Miss Piggy's Surname?",
        "Answer": "Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Father Peter Clifford in Ballykissangel?",
        "Answer": "Stephen Tompkinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Hyacinth Bucket in 'Keeping Up Appearances'?",
        "Answer": "Patricia Routledge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which fictional character has been played by Albert Finney, Peter Ustinov and David Suchet?",
        "Answer": "Hercule Poirot"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Coronation Street', which band was Les Battersby's a big fan of?",
        "Answer": "Status Quo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor starred in 'Rooster Cogburn'?",
        "Answer": "John Wayne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who presented 'The Sooty Show' in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "Matthew Corbett"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the animated film 'Thumbelina', who sang 'Let Me Be Your Wings'?",
        "Answer": "Barry Manilow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the animated Disney 1941 film 'Dumbo', who was the title characters best friend?",
        "Answer": "Timothy Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Basil Fawlty in 'Fawlty Towers'?",
        "Answer": "John Cleese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who co-stars with Matthew McConaughey in the film 'Two for the Money'?",
        "Answer": "Al Pacino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played Dr. Peter Venkman in 'Ghostbusters'?",
        "Answer": "Bill Murray"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Count Olaf in the film Lemony Snicke's A Series Of Unfortunate Events'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Carey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian played the lead character in 'The Man Who Sued God'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Connolly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1983 movie did Sean Connery return as James Bond?",
        "Answer": "Never Say Never Again"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Royston Vasey is the fictional town in the League of Gentlemen but it is also the real name of which comedian?",
        "Answer": "Roy 'Chubby' Brown"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What song is played at the end of the 1996 film 'A Life Less Ordinary' starring Cameron Diaz and Ewan McGregor?",
        "Answer": "Oasis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Father Dougall in the TV sitcom 'Father Ted'?",
        "Answer": "Ardal O'Hanlon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film sees the character Henri Charriere repeatedly try to escape from prison?",
        "Answer": "Papillion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series could have been called 'Truman and Adler'?",
        "Answer": "Will and Grace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Gerry Anderson TV show, who was the sheriff of 'Four Feather Falls'?",
        "Answer": "Tex Tucker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Gerry Anderson character worked for the World Intelligence Network?",
        "Answer": "Joe 90"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What craft would you expect Steve Zodiac to be in?",
        "Answer": "Fireball XL5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Gerry Anderson TV show, who was the sheriff of 'Four Feather Falls'?",
        "Answer": "Tex Tucker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Thunderbirds, what was Lady Penelope's surname?",
        "Answer": "Creighton-Ward"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Stingray what did WASP stand for?",
        "Answer": "World Aquanaut Security Patrol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was stung in 'The Sting'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Shaw"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose last film role was Mr Bridger in 'The Italian Job'?",
        "Answer": "Noel Coward's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor married singer Dorothy Squires in 1953, who was 12 years older than him?",
        "Answer": "Roger Moore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1972 film features the song 'Dueling Banjos'?",
        "Answer": "Deliverance"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film character has been played by Jack Lord, Cec Linder, Rik Van Nutter, Norman Burton, David Hedison, John Terry, David Hedison and Jeffrey Wright?",
        "Answer": "Felix Leiter (a character in James Bond films)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Dr. Duncan Waring in the 1970's TV series 'Doctor in the House'?",
        "Answer": "Robin Nedwell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Man on the Moon' was the biopic of which US comedian?",
        "Answer": "Andy Kaufman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1970s UK TV series did the character Charlie Endell appear?",
        "Answer": "Budgie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was in charge of the WASP submarine whose navigator was 'Phones' Sheridan?",
        "Answer": "Troy Tempest (in Stingray)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In \"Only Fools and Horses\", by what name did Trigger always call Rodney?",
        "Answer": "Dave"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first product to be advertised on ITV?",
        "Answer": "Toothpaste"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which three films did James Dean star in?",
        "Answer": "East of Eden, Rebel Without a Cause and Giant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor is godfather to actress Jennifer Anniston?",
        "Answer": "Telly Savalas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Melanie Griffith's famous actress mother?",
        "Answer": "Tippi Hedren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Liza Minnelli's famous actress mother?",
        "Answer": "Judy Garland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor is godfather to actress Jennifer Anniston?",
        "Answer": "Telly Savalas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Emilio Estevez's famous actor father?",
        "Answer": "Martin Sheen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film director is uncle to actor Nicolas Cage?",
        "Answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Angelna Jolie's famous actor father?",
        "Answer": "Jon Voigt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is actress Shirley Maclaine's famous actor brother?",
        "Answer": "Warren Beatty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Jamie-Lee Curtis's famous mother?",
        "Answer": "Janet Leigh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Ealing Comedies did Alec Guinness play Sid Stratton?",
        "Answer": "The Man in the White Suit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV series did Arthur Lowe play Father Duddleswell?",
        "Answer": "Bless Me Father"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Klunk, Zilly and which double act made up the Vulture Squadron in a childrens TV show?",
        "Answer": "Dick Dastardly and Muttley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Dawn French's character in 'The Vicar of Dibley'?",
        "Answer": "Geraldine Grainger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Eastenders, The Queen Victoria pub is on the corner of Albert Square and which other road?",
        "Answer": "Bridge Street"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the law firm that Ally McBeal worked for?",
        "Answer": "Fish and Cage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played the title role in 'Oh no! It's Selwyn Froggatt?'",
        "Answer": "Bill Maynard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British born actor was born with the name James Stewart?",
        "Answer": "Stewart Grainger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What character did Christopher Lee play in two \"Star Wars\" movies?",
        "Answer": "Count Dooku"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Doctor Who, who was the creator of the Daleks?",
        "Answer": "Davros"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Waylon Jennings song 'Good Ol Boys' was used as the theme tune to which TV show?",
        "Answer": "The Dukes Of Hazzard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Manuel in 'Fawlty Towers'?",
        "Answer": "Andrew Sachs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the American actor who played Ike Turner in 'Whats Love Got to Do With It' and Morpheous in 'The Matrix'?",
        "Answer": "Laurence Fishburne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the scarecrow in 'Bob The Builder'?",
        "Answer": "Spud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the scarecrow in 'Bob The Builder'?",
        "Answer": "Spud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Eric Spear is best known for composing the music to which long running TV show?",
        "Answer": "Coronation Street"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Bridget Jones Diary' what colour is the soup that she serves to her friend at a dinner party?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy 'Bread' what was the name of the Boswells daughter?",
        "Answer": "Aveline"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name did Tom Hanks give to his volleyball companion in the film 'Cast Away'?",
        "Answer": "Wilson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the most nominated actor for an Oscar?",
        "Answer": "Jack Nicholson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the company that Reginald Perrin worked for in the TV series 'The Fall And Rise Of Reginald Perrin'?",
        "Answer": "Sunshine Desserts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which video game and film takes place in Racoon City?",
        "Answer": "Resident Evil"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which series of horror films take place in the fictional town of Springwood, Ohio?",
        "Answer": "Nightmare On Elm Street"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical film takes place in Denton, Ohio?",
        "Answer": "The Rocky Horror Picture Show"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Australian film does the town of Porpoise Spit feature?",
        "Answer": "Muriel's Wedding"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What character does Alan Fletcher play in 'Neighbours'?",
        "Answer": "Dr Karl Kennedy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the cat who chased Pixie and Dixie?",
        "Answer": "Mr Jinx"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the band on The Muppet Show?",
        "Answer": "Doctor Teeth and the Electric Mayhem"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Question or Nominate' was a phrase commonly heard on which UK TV quiz show?",
        "Answer": "Fifteen-to-one"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the maximum achievable score in Fifteen-to-one?",
        "Answer": "433, 10 pts for each of all 40 questions, 10 pts each life, 3 pts for lives from 1st and 2nd rounds"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who pilots Thunderbird 1?",
        "Answer": "Scott Tracy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1970s musical film starred Angela Lansbury as a trainee witch?",
        "Answer": "Bedknobs and Broomsticks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy 'One Foot in the Grave' what is the name of Victor Meldrew's wife?",
        "Answer": "Margaret"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade was the film 'Grease' set?",
        "Answer": "1950s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy 'One Foot in the Grave' what is the name of Victor Meldrew's wife?",
        "Answer": "Margaret"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did ITV start broadcasting?",
        "Answer": "1955"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the character name of the 'Saint'?",
        "Answer": "Simon Templar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the surname of the character in the 60's drama 'Man In A Suitcase'?",
        "Answer": "McGill"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the dog in the American TV sit-com 'Mad About You'?",
        "Answer": "Murray"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the stage name of Ian and Janet Tough?",
        "Answer": "The Krankies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Wizard Of Oz, what is Dorothy's surname?",
        "Answer": "Gale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which late Hollywood actor was born Roy Scherer",
        "Answer": "rock hudson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the first names of 'The Blues Brothers'?",
        "Answer": "Jake and Elwood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'The Saint' what was the full name of the main character?",
        "Answer": "Simon Templar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Andy Pandy' what was Andy's sister's name?",
        "Answer": "Mandy Pandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the housekeeper in Father Ted?",
        "Answer": "Mrs Doyle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Rene Artois in 'Allo Allo'?",
        "Answer": "Gordon Kaye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of Disney's Seven Dwarfs wore glasses?",
        "Answer": "Doc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played the love interest opposite Tobey Maguire in the Spiderman films?",
        "Answer": "Kirsten Dunst"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the police officer in the cartoon Top Cat?",
        "Answer": "Officer Dibble"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film and TV series 'The Fugitive' what was the occupation of the Fugitive?",
        "Answer": "Doctor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the leading role in the 1986 film 'The Fly'?",
        "Answer": "Jeff Goldblum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote the TV series 'Only Fools And Horses'?",
        "Answer": "John Sullivan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Hakuna Matata' was a song from which 1994 Disney film?",
        "Answer": "The Lion King"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What species is Gizmo in the 'Gremlins' movies?",
        "Answer": "Mogwai"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Lone Ranger' what was Tonto's horse called?",
        "Answer": "Scout"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the final word spoken in the 1939 film 'The Wizard Of Oz'?",
        "Answer": "Home"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'Fawlty Towers' from which city does the waiter Manuel hail?",
        "Answer": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which TV show might you have seen Statler and Waldorf?",
        "Answer": "The Muppet Show"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the local newspaper in the TV show 'Only Fools And Horses'?",
        "Answer": "The Peckham Echo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor worked as a translator for the Swedish hockey team during the 1980 winter olympics?",
        "Answer": "Viggo Mortensen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Disney's  'Beauty And The Beast', what is Beauty's name?",
        "Answer": "Belle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Lord Of The Rings' star is also an accomplished poet, artist, photographer and jazz musician?",
        "Answer": "Viggo Mortensen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the main character in the 1986 film 'Troll'? Harry Potter, Bridget Jones or Tinky Winky?",
        "Answer": "Harry Potter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980s movie featured a hero named Atreyu?",
        "Answer": "The Neverending Story"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which movie did Vincent Price make his last appearance?",
        "Answer": "Edward Scissorhands"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actress was the part of Dorothy in 'The Wizard Of Oz' originally intended for?",
        "Answer": "Shirley Temple"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was the character of Dorothy in the film 'The Wizard Of Oz'?",
        "Answer": "17"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Liverpool born entertainer had the real name of Maurice Cole?",
        "Answer": "Kenny Everett"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was a member of both the Dirty Dozen and The Magnificent Seven?",
        "Answer": "Charles Bronson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sung the theme tune for the film 'Goldeneye'?",
        "Answer": "Tina Turner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The childrens TV character Prince Adam of Eternia is better known by what name?",
        "Answer": "He-Man"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the estate in the TV show 'Monarch Of The Glen'?",
        "Answer": "Glenbogle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 2 Bond films does the character of Jaws appear?",
        "Answer": "The Spy Who Loved Me and Moonraker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On TV, what is Father Ted's Surname?",
        "Answer": "Crilly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first Hollywood actress to demand and receive a fee of 1 million dollars for a single film role?",
        "Answer": "Elizabeth Taylor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous comedian used the name Gerald Wiley when he submitted scripts to the BBC?",
        "Answer": "Ronnie Barker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon characters name is Italian for 'pine eye'?",
        "Answer": "Pinocchio"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the Carry On film featured the '3rd Foot And Mouth Regiment', the 'Devils In Skirts'?",
        "Answer": "Carry On Up The Khyber"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV cartoon were there female characters who had the maiden names Slaghoopal and Jean McBricker?",
        "Answer": "The Flintstones (Wilma and Betty's maiden names)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The episode of 'The Simpsons' which guest starred U2, is dedicated to which other star who had guested on the show?",
        "Answer": "Linda McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did a dog called Bruiser Woods first appear?",
        "Answer": "Legally Blonde"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the sitcom Friends, which character has the middle name Muriel?",
        "Answer": "Chandler"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the names of the five Marx brothers?",
        "Answer": "Chico, Harpo, Groucho, Gummo and Zeppo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Groucho Marx's real first name? Julius, Constantine or Victor?",
        "Answer": "Julius"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'B' was the name of the mechanical shark used in the original 'Jaws' film?",
        "Answer": "Bruce"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor links the film 'Predator' with the first four 'Rocky' films?",
        "Answer": "Carl Weathers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Coronation Street' who plays Mike Baldwin?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Briggs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Talia Shire was nominated for a Best Actress Oscar for playing the wife of which well known movie character?",
        "Answer": "Rocky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 2004 Blockbuster 'Troy' what is the name of the character played by Brad Pitt?",
        "Answer": "Achilles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Michelle McManus found her fame on which TV show?",
        "Answer": "Pop Idol"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the male lead in the 1986 film 'The Fly'?",
        "Answer": "Jeff Goldblum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the surname of bartender Moe in 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Syzlak"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor won an oscar for his portrail of Ray Charles in the 2004 film 'Ray'?",
        "Answer": "Jamie Foxx"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1960s series 'The Man from Uncle' who played Napoleon Solo?",
        "Answer": "Robert Vaughn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was first to play 'Dr Who' on TV?",
        "Answer": "William Hartnell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress links the 1989 film 'Tango and Cash' and the TV series 'Desperate Housewives'?",
        "Answer": "Teri Hatcher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the surname of bartender Moe in 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Syzlak"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Good the Bad And The Ugly' who played 'The Bad'?",
        "Answer": "Lee Van Cleef"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sarah Jessica Parker is famous for her role in 'Sex and the City', but who did she star alongside in the 1993 film 'Striking Distance'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Seven' what is the name of the killer played by Kevin Spacey?",
        "Answer": "John Doe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at September 2005, what Hollywood blockbuster has taken more money at the box office in the US than any other film?",
        "Answer": "Titanic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which fictional TV character runs a production company called Peartree Productions?",
        "Answer": "Alan Partridge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series of the same name, what does 'C. S. I.' stand for?",
        "Answer": "Crime Scene Investigation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Die Hard films what is the name of Bruce Willis' character",
        "Answer": "John McClane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Out of the 6 Star Wars films, which has made the most money at the US Box office?",
        "Answer": "Star Wars IV: A New Hope"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Gladiator'?",
        "Answer": "Ridley Scott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Prescription: Murder' was the title of the first ever episode of which TV show?",
        "Answer": "Columbo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which producer is responsible for 'Pearl Harbour', 'Pirates of the Caribbean', and 'Armageddon'?",
        "Answer": "Jerry Bruckheimer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the cartoon world, who has a cousin called Slowpoke Rodriguez?",
        "Answer": "Speedy Gonzales"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Julie Andrews middle name? Eleanor, Elizabeth or Julie?",
        "Answer": "Elizabeth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Dallas' who shot J. R. Ewing?",
        "Answer": "Kristin Shepard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Justin Henry becamse the youngest actor to be nominated for Oscar after his performance in which 1979 film?",
        "Answer": "Kramer vs Kramer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Dallas character did Terry Wogan nickname the 'poisoned dwarf'?",
        "Answer": "Lucy Ewing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Dallas character did Terry Wogan nickname the 'poisoned dwarf'?",
        "Answer": "Lucy Ewing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Luke Skywalker in 'Star Wars'?",
        "Answer": "Mark Hamill"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Zahara and Maddox are the adopted children of which Hollywood star?",
        "Answer": "Angelina Jolie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous musician played the part of Curtis in 'The Blues Brothers'?",
        "Answer": "Cab Calloway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor is the last surviving actor of 'The Magnificent Seven'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Vaughn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sergeant Bilko was a character in which US TV show?",
        "Answer": "The Phil Silvers Show"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Morgan Freeman play an inmate called Red?",
        "Answer": "The Shawshank Redemption"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the names of Thermoman's children?",
        "Answer": "Ollie and Cassie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1990 film do the characters Edward Lewis and Vivian Ward appear?",
        "Answer": "Pretty Woman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the pilot of Thunderbird 4?",
        "Answer": "Gordon Tracy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV Character's classic lines include 'Time's Fun When You're Having Flies' and 'It's Not Easy Being Green'?",
        "Answer": "Kermit The Frog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the singer Michael Barrett better known?",
        "Answer": "Shakin Stevens"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV series did a mule called 'Number 7' appear?",
        "Answer": "The Life And Times Of Grizzly Adams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Jerry in the film 'Jerry McGuire'?",
        "Answer": "Tom Cruise"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What do the letters OC stand for in the programme The OC?",
        "Answer": "Orange County"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', which actor and comedian provies the voice of Bart's arch enemy Sideshow Bob?",
        "Answer": "Kelsey Grammer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Bart Simpson's dog?",
        "Answer": "Santa's Little Helper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous female character of TV and films was played by a male when she was first introduced to our screens in 1943?",
        "Answer": "Lassie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Womble was named after a South American river?",
        "Answer": "Orinoco"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1997, which movie star agreed to take the lead role in 'Cop Land' for a fee of just $60,000 in order to play a serious role?",
        "Answer": "Sylvester Stallone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When Deryck Guyler's character in 'Sykes' had his hat on he was Constable Turnbull, but what were Eric and Hattie allowed to call him when he wasn't wearing his hat?",
        "Answer": "Corky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following TV shows has a theme tune which doesn't mention the show's name in the song? Sesame Street, The Dukes Of Hazzard or Wonder Woman?",
        "Answer": "The Dukes Of Hazzard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'P. M.' is the name of the lawyer who never loses a case in 'The Flintstones'?",
        "Answer": "Perry Masonry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is the villain Sylvester Sneekly better known?",
        "Answer": "The Hooded Claw"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the 1st Oscar winning film to feature no women?",
        "Answer": "Lawrence of Arabia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Life Of Brian', what was Brian's mother's name?",
        "Answer": "Mandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the connection between actor Nicholas Cage and director Soffia Coppola?",
        "Answer": "They are cousins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed Natural Born Killers?",
        "Answer": "Oliver Stone (It was only written by Quentin Tarantino)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Evil Edna, Mavis Cruet, The Moog, Carwash and Arthur were characters in which children's TV programme?",
        "Answer": "Willo the Wisp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was actor Joaquin Pheonix's original christian name?",
        "Answer": "Leaf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor's real name is Michael Douglas but had to change it for obvious reasons?",
        "Answer": "Michael Keaton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Talia Shire, who plays 'Adrian' in the Rocky movies, is the sister of which famous movie director?",
        "Answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor had a small role in 'Robin Hood: Prince Of Thieves' and donated his fee for the film to charity?",
        "Answer": "Sean Connery"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Eddie Murphy will always be remembered for Axel Foley from the Beverly Hills Cop movies, but which famous actor was originally signed up to play the role?",
        "Answer": "Sylvester Stallone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was subtitled ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃâHow I learned to stop worrying and love the bombÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃÂ?",
        "Answer": "Dr Strangelove"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was significant about Lance Henriksen's characters in 'Aliens' and 'Alien vs Predator'?",
        "Answer": "In Alien he played 'Bishop' the android. In 'Alien vs Predator' he played Charles Bishop Weyland, the founder of the company who created the androids."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At the Academy Awards in February 2005, who won the Oscar for Best Actress?",
        "Answer": "Hilary Swank"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At the Academy Awards in February 2005, which film won the Oscar for Best Animated Feature?",
        "Answer": "The Incredibles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the dinosaur in 'The Flintstones'?",
        "Answer": "Dino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors appeared together in the films 'Meet The Parents', 'Zoolander', 'The Royal Tennenbaums' and 'Cable Guy'?",
        "Answer": "Ben Stiller & Owen Wilson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Why was Carole Hersee regularly seen on BBC television in the 1960ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s and 1970ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s?",
        "Answer": "She was the girl on the BBC Test Card"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980's film was based on Philip Dick's 1968 novel 'Do Androids Dream Of Electric Sheep'?",
        "Answer": "Blade Runner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Austin Powers middle name?",
        "Answer": "Danger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor makes a cameo appearance in the film 'Planes, Trains and Automobiles' where he races Steve Martin for a taxi in rush hour?",
        "Answer": "Kevin Bacon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the original name of Mickey Mouse?",
        "Answer": "Mortimer Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is actress Isabella Rossellini's famous mother?",
        "Answer": "Ingrid Bergman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mickey Mouse is named after the son of Walt Disney's girlfriend, who later went on to be a famous film actor. Who is he?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Rooney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the title of the Kill Bill Vol 1 Theme Tune that has been used widely since the films release?",
        "Answer": "Battle Without Honour Or Humanity (By Tomayasu Hotel)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Simspon voice regular and secondary character movie actor was shot dead by his wife in 1998?",
        "Answer": "Phil Hartman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which name links a Batman villain played by Christopher Walken and a character played by Mike Myers?",
        "Answer": "Shrek"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Batman in the 1992 film 'Batman Returns'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Keaton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous British actress' father created the British version of the TV show 'The Magic Roundabout'?",
        "Answer": "Emma Thompson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 'Batman' film features Jim Carrey and Nicole Kidman?",
        "Answer": "'Batman Forever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Eastenders' character was played by Paul Bradley?",
        "Answer": "Nigel Bates"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor/director said in 1989 'I don't go around saying: 'Hello, did you know I'm the new Olivier?''?",
        "Answer": "Kenneth Branagh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1983 film, based on a novel by Stephen King, features a dog with rabies?",
        "Answer": "'Cujo'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1995 film starred Robert De Niro, Al Pacino and Val Kilmer?",
        "Answer": "Heat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animated TV character said 'I'm not normally a religious man, but if you're up there, save me, Superman'?",
        "Answer": "Homer Simpson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does Harrison Ford play the character of Dr. Norman Spencer?",
        "Answer": "'What Lies Beneath'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 3 spaghetti westerns, did director Sergio Leone make that starred Clint Eastwood as the cowboy with no name?",
        "Answer": "Fistfull of dollars; For A Few Dollars More; The Good, The Bad, and the Ugly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In November 2002, which actor married the Bond girl Carey Lowell in New York?",
        "Answer": "Richard Gere"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which famous film would first have come across the character of Dorothy Gale?",
        "Answer": "The Wizard Of Oz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Austin Powers In Goldmember', what is the first name of Austin's father?",
        "Answer": "Nigel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Carrie in the 1976 horror film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Sissy Spacek"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Huckleberry Hound's favourite song?",
        "Answer": "'My Darling Clementine'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed and starred in the film which won the best picture Oscar in 1991?",
        "Answer": "Kevin Costner (for 'Dances With Wolves')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons' what were Bart Simpson's first words?",
        "Answer": "'Ay Carumba'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV character was sent to Earth as punishment for drawing a moustache on a picture of the 'Solar Leader'?",
        "Answer": "Mork (from 'Mork and Mindy')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1967 film did the character Lucas Jackson appear, and who played him?",
        "Answer": "'Cool Hand Luke', Paul Newman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does the character of Honey Rider appear?",
        "Answer": "'Dr No'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the only British film to win the Palme D'Or award at the Cannes film festival in the 1990s?",
        "Answer": "'Secrets And Lies'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the dog that befriended Kevin Costner in 'Dances With Wolves'?",
        "Answer": "Two Socks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1997 film featured Batman and Robin battling against Mr Freeze and Poison Ivy?",
        "Answer": "'Batman and Robin'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1960 western was based on the film 'The Seven Samurai'?",
        "Answer": "'The Magnificent Seven'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1938 film 'Going Places', Louis Armstrong sung the song 'Jeepers Creepers'. Who or what was 'Jeepers Creepers'?",
        "Answer": "A racehorse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bob Hope was born in which country?",
        "Answer": "England"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What Walt Disney film was the first to combine visual images with concert music?",
        "Answer": "'Fantasia'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Courtney Cox's news reporter in the 'Scream' films?",
        "Answer": "Gale Weathers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many Oscar nominations did Titanic receive?",
        "Answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The theft of a painting by Monet forms part of the plot for which 1999 film?",
        "Answer": "The Thomas Crown Affair"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How did Victor Meldrew die in the last episode of 'One Foot in the Grave'?",
        "Answer": "He was knocked down by a hit and run driver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the only X rated film to win the best picture award at the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'Midnight Cowboy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character played by Leslie Neilson in the 'Naked Gun' films?",
        "Answer": "Lt Frank Drebbin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1915 film, directed by D.W.Griffith, was seen as a landmark in American movies?",
        "Answer": "'The Birth Of A Nation'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which cartoon series would you associate 'The Buzzwagon', 'The Crimson Haybayler' and 'The Mean Machine'?",
        "Answer": "'Wacky Races'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the ship that Captain Pugwash sailed in?",
        "Answer": "The Black Pig"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian plays the character of Paul Calf on television?",
        "Answer": "Steve Coogan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Arnold Swarzenegger say 'I'll be back' for the first time?",
        "Answer": "'The Terminator'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the title role in the 2002 film 'Mr Deeds'?",
        "Answer": "Adam Sandler"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the cartoon series 'Wacky Races', who drove the 'Compact Pussycat'?",
        "Answer": "Penelope Pitstop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which director was nominated for an Oscar for the 1998 film 'The Truman Show'?",
        "Answer": "Peter Weir"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1967, who appeared on the first cover of Rolling Stone magazine?",
        "Answer": "John Lennon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1980 film 'The Blues Brothers'?",
        "Answer": "John Landis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animal is associated with the beginning of an MGM film?",
        "Answer": "A lion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American rock star played a bus driver in the Spice Girls movie 'Spiceworld'?",
        "Answer": "Meatloaf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which football team did Alf Garnett support in the TV show 'Till Death Do Us Part'?",
        "Answer": "West Ham United"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Fierce Creatures' was the follow up to which film?",
        "Answer": "'A Fish Called Wanda'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title roles in the 1991 film 'Frankie and Johnny'?",
        "Answer": "Michelle Pfieffer and Al Pacino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred in the title role in the 1992 film 'Chaplin'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Downey Jr."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British actor played Lee Harvey Oswald in the 1991 film 'JFK'?",
        "Answer": "Gary Oldman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the profession of Patrick Swayze's character in 'Ghost'?",
        "Answer": "Stockbroker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which James Bond film caused controversy over the spelling of it's title, when Americans wanted a letter 'c' where the British wanted a letter 's'?",
        "Answer": "'License To Kill'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Marilyn Monroe's characters' first name in the film 'Some Like It Hot'?",
        "Answer": "Sugar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the profession of Fay Wray's character in the 1933 film 'King Kong'? Journalist, Writer or Actress?",
        "Answer": "Actress"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', who replaced Sideshow Bob?",
        "Answer": "Sideshow Mel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1987 film 'The Untouchables'?",
        "Answer": "Brian De Palma"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Flintstones', what is Barney's wife called?",
        "Answer": "Betty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is most of the British horror film 'Dog Soldiers' set?",
        "Answer": "Scotland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was one of 'The Dirty Dozen' and 'The Magnificent Seven'?",
        "Answer": "Charles Bronson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following film directors once owned a dog called Indiana? Steven Spielberg, George Lucas or Richard Attenborough?",
        "Answer": "George Lucas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Pussy Galore in the James Bond film 'Goldfinger'?",
        "Answer": "Honor Blackman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Rogue Trader', starring Ewan McGregor, is based around the life of which real life person?",
        "Answer": "Nick Leeson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who are the male and female leads in the 1961 film 'Breakfast At Tiffany's'?",
        "Answer": "George Peppard and Audrey Hepburn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What did Marilyn Monroe say was the only thing she wore in bed?",
        "Answer": "Chanel No. 5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what profession did Harrison Ford make a living before making it big as an actor?",
        "Answer": "Carpenter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Daily Wine Deals' is an anagram of which famous actor?",
        "Answer": "Daniel Day Lewis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film features children called Jane and Michael who live at 17 Cherry Tree Lane?",
        "Answer": "'Mary Poppins'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following actors does not appear in the film 'The Royal Tenenbaums'? Gene Hackman, Ben Affleck or Ben Stiller?",
        "Answer": "Ben Affleck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the credits of a film, how is the assistant to the gaffer commonly referred?",
        "Answer": "Best Boy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animal would you associate with the start of a film by the studio MGM?",
        "Answer": "Lion"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not star in the 1990 film 'Miller's Crossing'? Ned Beatty, Albert Finney or Gabriel Byrne?",
        "Answer": "Ned Beatty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1999 film is based on the novel 'Les liaisons dangereuses'?",
        "Answer": "'Cruel Intentions'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the sequel to the film 'Saturday Night Fever' called?",
        "Answer": "'Staying Alive'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the 1983 film 'Scarface'?",
        "Answer": "Al Pacino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which television programme would you have found Louby Loo?",
        "Answer": "Andy Pandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the names of the characters played by Clark Gable and Vivien Leigh in 'Gone With The Wind'?",
        "Answer": "Rhett Butler and Scarlet O'Hara"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'A Bridge Too Far'?",
        "Answer": "Richard Attenbrough"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played a character who was frozen for 50 years in the film 'Forever Young'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Gibson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Kavanagh QC on British television?",
        "Answer": "John Thaw"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the film 'Edward Scissorhands'?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Depp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did actress Grace Kelly marry in 1956?",
        "Answer": "Prince Rainier of Monaco"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Alfred Hitchcock's first film to be filmed in colour rather than black and white?",
        "Answer": "'Rope'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress married and divorced both Mickey Rooney and Frank Sinatra?",
        "Answer": "Ava Gardner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1995 film did Sylvester Stallone play the title character, who was adapted from a comic book?",
        "Answer": "'Judge Dredd'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Bill Murray play a character who keeps reliving the same day over and over again?",
        "Answer": "'Groundhog Day'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the role of Tom Hanks' gay lover in the film 'Philadelphia'?",
        "Answer": "Antonio Banderas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who designed Elizabeth Hurley's famous dress which she wore to the premiere of the film 'Four Weddings And A Funeral'?",
        "Answer": "Gianni Versace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What kind of creature is Sebastian in 'The Little Mermaid'?",
        "Answer": "Crab"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which English city is 'One Foot In The Grave' set?",
        "Answer": "Bournemouth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How was Benjamin Franklin Pierce better known in the TV show 'M*A*S*H'?",
        "Answer": "Hawkeye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film about Vietnam won the best picture at the Oscar ceremony in 1979?",
        "Answer": "The Deer Hunter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Tom Hanks play a prison guard called Paul Edgecomb?",
        "Answer": "'The Green Mile'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How was Benjamin Franklin Pierce better known in the TV show 'M*A*S*H'?",
        "Answer": "Hawkeye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of film director George Lucas' dog which lended it's name to a famous film character?",
        "Answer": "Indiana"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 3 films did James Dean star?",
        "Answer": "'East Of Eden', 'Rebel Without A Cause' and 'Giant'."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', Fallout Boy is the side-kick to who?",
        "Answer": "Radioactive Man"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what is the name of Ned Flanders wife?",
        "Answer": "Maude"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 2000 film would you find the character of General Maximus Decimus Meridus?",
        "Answer": "'Gladiator'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directred the film 'Apocalypse Now'?",
        "Answer": "Francis Ford Copolla"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does Michelle Pfeiffer play the character of Catwoman?",
        "Answer": "Batman Returns"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played John Malkovich in the film 'Being John Malkovich'?",
        "Answer": "John Malkovich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Leslie Neilson's character in the 'Police Squad' TV series and 'Naked Gun' films?",
        "Answer": "Frank Drebin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Little Jackie Paper was the human friend of which famous fictional character?",
        "Answer": "Puff the Magic Dragon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the names of the four films made by the pop group the Beatles?",
        "Answer": "'A Hard Days Night', 'Help', 'Yellow Submarine' and 'Let It Be'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What day of the week provides the name of one of the children in 'The Addams Family'?",
        "Answer": "Wednesday"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The TV series 'Dynasty' was set in which American city?",
        "Answer": "Denver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Rooster Cogburn' was the sequel to what film starring John Wayne?",
        "Answer": "'True Grit'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1992 film had the tagline 'The Bat, the Cat, the Penguin'?",
        "Answer": "Batman Returns"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2001, how many best director Oscars has Martin Scorcese won?",
        "Answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which series of erotic films shot Sylvia Krystal to fame in the 70s?",
        "Answer": "'Emmanuelle'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not star in Alfred Hitchcock's film 'The Birds'? Donna Reed, Jessica Tandy or Tippi Hedren?",
        "Answer": "Donna Reed"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Disney film was inspired by a fairy tale by author Charles Perrault?",
        "Answer": "'Cinderalla'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was advertised with the slogans 'Collide with destiny' and 'Nothing on Earth could come between them'?",
        "Answer": "'Titanic'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What two words usually begin the names of the episodes of the TV show 'Friends'?",
        "Answer": "'The one'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character played by Kevin Costner in the film 'JFK'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Garrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the dog in 'The Grinch Who Stole Christmas'? Ben, Max or Rod?",
        "Answer": "Max"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On TV, how were Fleegle, Snorky, Bingo and Drooper better known collectively?",
        "Answer": "'The Banana Splits'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series features a store called 'The Leftorium'?",
        "Answer": "'The Simpsons'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1980s film did Darryl Hannah play a mermaid?",
        "Answer": "'Splash'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which superhero has a butler named Alfred?",
        "Answer": "Batman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city was the US TV series 'Ironside' set?",
        "Answer": "San Francisco"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two brothers played the title roles in the 1990 film 'The Krays'?",
        "Answer": "Gary Kemp and Martin Kemp."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Chariots Of Fire' is based around the Olympics of what year?",
        "Answer": "1924"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV show featured the character of DS Jane Penhaligon?",
        "Answer": "'Cracker'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character in the television series 'London's Burning' was played by Richard Walsh? Sick note, Four eyes or Rent boy?",
        "Answer": "Sick-note"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What famous cartoon character was born on April 1st, 1980?",
        "Answer": "Bart Simpson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1980 film was advertised with the line 'They'll never get caught. They're on a mission from God.'",
        "Answer": "'The Blues Brothers'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Marilyn Monroe die?",
        "Answer": "1962"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film are Peter Fonda, Dennis Hopper and Jack Nicholson said to be smoking real marijauna on camera?",
        "Answer": "'Easy Rider'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film did Henry Fonda receive his last Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'On Golden Pond'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film did Henry Fonda receive his last Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'On Golden Pond'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which seaside town was the TV show 'Fawlty Towers' set?",
        "Answer": "Torquay"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Bonnie in the 1967 film 'Bonnie And Clyde'?",
        "Answer": "Faye Dunaway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'The Simpsons', who or what is Santa's Little Helper?",
        "Answer": "Their pet dog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1984 film starred Bill Murray, Dan Aykroyd and Sigourney Weaver?",
        "Answer": "'Ghostbusters'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Spiderman', what is the name of the newspaper where Peter Parker works as a photographer?",
        "Answer": "The Daily Bugle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to a 1998 poll of filmmakers conducted by the American Film Institute, what 1941 film ranked as the greatest film of all time?",
        "Answer": "'Citizen Kane'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the cartoon series 'The Simpsons', what musical instrument does Lisa Simpson play?",
        "Answer": "The saxophone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what was Maggie's first word?",
        "Answer": "'Daddy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the main villain in 'Die Hard: With A Vengeance'?",
        "Answer": "Jeremy Irons"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1979 features characters called Ripley, Dallas, Brett and Lambert?",
        "Answer": "Alien"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the secret identity of the comic book character Babs Gordon?",
        "Answer": "Batgirl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is the fictional 'Charles Townsend Associates Pvt. Detective Agency' better known?",
        "Answer": "Charlie's Angels"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980's film had the tag-line 'He is afraid. He is alone. He is three million light years from home.'?",
        "Answer": "'E.T.'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the movie world, how is Nicholas Kim Coppola better known?",
        "Answer": "Nicolas Cage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which newspaper did Superman work?",
        "Answer": "The Daily Planet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played John Brown in the film 'Mrs Brown'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Connolly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the Tim Burton film 'Ed Wood'?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Depp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many children were there in 'The Partridge Family'?",
        "Answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the 'Blues Brother' star who died of a drug overdose in 1982?",
        "Answer": "John Belushi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Star Trek', what is the nickname of Dr McCoy?",
        "Answer": "Bones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor in his autobiography said 'All I need to make a comedy is a park, a policeman and a pretty girl'?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the surname of the family who employed Julie Andrews' character in the film 'The Sound Of Music'?",
        "Answer": "Von Trappe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the city in which The Simpsons live?",
        "Answer": "Springfield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first animal film star?",
        "Answer": "Rin Tin Tin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the original 'Big Brother', who was the first person to be voted out?",
        "Answer": "Sada"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV series might you have found the 'Pacific Princess'?",
        "Answer": "Love Boat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Tom Cruise's character in 'Mission Impossible'?",
        "Answer": "Ethan Hunt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was confirmed as new BBC Chairman in April 2004?",
        "Answer": "Michael Grade"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1976 film about a boxer won an Oscar for Best Picture?",
        "Answer": "'Rocky'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which English city is the film 'The Full Monty' set?",
        "Answer": "Sheffield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What sport features in the films 'He Got Game' (1998), 'Flubber' (1997) and 'Celtic Pride' (1996)?",
        "Answer": "Basketball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed 'The Killing Fields' and 'Chariots Of Fire'?",
        "Answer": "David Puttnam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won 'Celebrity Big Brother' on Channel 4 in 2002?",
        "Answer": "Mark Owen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the maximum number of people that could be 'beamed up' into the Starship Enterprise from Star Trek in one go?",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What name was given to films in the 1930s, 40s and 50s which were made as a companion to a main feature in a double bill program?",
        "Answer": "B-movies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many best actress Oscars has Katherine Hepburn won?",
        "Answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city is the Golden Bear film festival held?",
        "Answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name was the UK entertainer Alfred Hawthorne Hill better known?",
        "Answer": "Benny Hill"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the only TV cartoon dog to have an Antarctic island named after him?",
        "Answer": "Huckleberry Hound"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Eastenders, what are the names of Pauline Fowlers two sons?",
        "Answer": "Mark and Martin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the last James Bond film in which Roger Moore starred?",
        "Answer": "'A View To A Kill'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which duo starred in the Oscar winning films 'Quiet Please', 'The Little Orphan' and 'The Milky Way'?",
        "Answer": "Tom and Jerry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many Oscars did the film 'West Side Story' win?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which former 'Eastenders' actor narrated the TV series 'Paddington Green'?",
        "Answer": "Ross Kemp"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV show is centred around the firm of Wernham Hogg?",
        "Answer": "The Office"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which politician was once replaced by a tub of lard on the TV show 'Have I Got News for You'?",
        "Answer": "Roy Hattersley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which four fim stars formed 'United Artists' in 1919?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin, Douglas Fairbanks, Mary Pickford and D. W. Griffiths"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1988 film would you find the character of Hans Gruber?",
        "Answer": "Die Hard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played General George Custer in the film 'They Died With Their Boots On'?",
        "Answer": "Erroll Flynn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the follow up to the film 'Raiders Of The Lost Ark'?",
        "Answer": "'Indiana Jones And The Temple Of Doom'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade did Charlie Chaplin die?",
        "Answer": "1970s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which British TV show is there a pub called the Woolpack?",
        "Answer": "'Emmerdale'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What James Bond film was the first not be based on an Ian Fleming novel or short story?",
        "Answer": "'Goldeneye'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'All The President's Men' is set around which political scandal?",
        "Answer": "Watergate"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1961 film features the character of Holly Golightly?",
        "Answer": "'Breakfast At Tiffany's'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Queen Elizabeth I in 'Blackadder II'?",
        "Answer": "Miranda Richardson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Paul Eddington's character in the TV shows 'Yes, Minister' and 'Yes, Prime Minister'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Hacker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy series 'Blackadder', what was Blackadder's first name?",
        "Answer": "Edmund"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On a movie set, who or what is the gaffer?",
        "Answer": "The chief electrician"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who provided the voice of the baby in the film 'Look who's talking'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Marlon Brando complain to his brother that he was handed 'a one-way ticket to Palookaville'?",
        "Answer": "'On The Waterfront'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Marc Antony in the 1963 film 'Cleopatra'?",
        "Answer": "Richard Burton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city was the musical film 'Cabaret' set?",
        "Answer": "Berlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the real name of the comedian who plays the character of Ali G?",
        "Answer": "Sacha Baron Cohen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred in the film 'Enter The Dragon'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which part of his body does Jack Nicholson have bandaged for most of the film 'Chinatown'?",
        "Answer": "Nose"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV comedy might you see a horse called Hercules?",
        "Answer": "'Steptoe And Son'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film did Steven Spielberg win his first Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'Schindler's List'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Back To The Future'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Zemeckis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "During the filming of which movie did George Harrison of the Beatles meet his first wife Patti Boyd?",
        "Answer": "'A Hard Day's Night'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oscar winning actor provided the voice of Hopper in the film 'A Bug's Life'?",
        "Answer": "Kevin Spacey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what type of animal is Santa's Little Helper?",
        "Answer": "A Dog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV comedy show would you find Dave Lister?",
        "Answer": "'Red Dwarf'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Doctor Who', what was the name of the chief of the Daleks?",
        "Answer": "Davros"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who created the police drama series 'Prime Suspect'?",
        "Answer": "Lynda La Plante"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What character did Alicia Silverstone play in the 1997 film 'Batman and Robin'?",
        "Answer": "Batgirl"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the cartoon series 'Rocko's Modern Life' what kind of animal is Rocko?",
        "Answer": "Wallaby"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the first names of the two main characters in the film 'Grease'?",
        "Answer": "Danny and Sandy."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played the title role in the 1990 film 'Pretty Woman'?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not appear in the film 'Blue Velvet'? Kyle Maclachlan, Nicolas Cage or Laura Dern?",
        "Answer": "Nicolas Cage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which half of a famous comedy duo was born at Ulverston in the Lake District in 1890?",
        "Answer": "Stan Laurel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the subject of the 1958 film 'A Night To Remember'?",
        "Answer": "The sinking of the ship Titanic"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was unusual about the role that won Linda Hunt a Best Supporting Actress Oscar for the film 'The Year Of Living Dangerously'?",
        "Answer": "The character she played was male"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Russell Crowe make his American debut, appearing with Sharon Stone, Leonardo Di Caprio and Gene Hackman?",
        "Answer": "'The Quick And The Dead'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series was set in Kirby Newtown?",
        "Answer": "'Z Cars'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Doctor Who in just 31 episodes between 1984 and 1986?",
        "Answer": "Colin Baker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the character of 'Ferris Bueller' in the film 'Ferris Bueller's Day Off'?",
        "Answer": "Matther Broderick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1993 film does Bill Murray play Phil Connors?",
        "Answer": "'Groundhog Day'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was an adaptation of a Michael Ondaajte novel and won 9 Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'The English Patient'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor turned singer had a UK number one hit single with 'Ain't No Doubt' in 1992?",
        "Answer": "Jimmy Nail"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played 'The Talented Mr Ripley' in a 1999 film?",
        "Answer": "Matt Damon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Australian city is the TV soap opera 'Neighbours' set?",
        "Answer": "Melbourne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the Marx brothers was the silent one?",
        "Answer": "Harpo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'A.I.' was completed by director Steven Spielberg, but which director started the project?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who narrated the BBC childrens TV show 'The Wombles'?",
        "Answer": "Bernard Cribbins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 2001 film 'Mulholland Dr.' who the twin role of Betty and Diane?",
        "Answer": "Naomi Watts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1997, what took over from 'The Flintstones' as the longest running prime-time animated series?",
        "Answer": "'The Simpsons'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two films that have won best picture Oscar's in the 1990s have types of animals in their title?",
        "Answer": "'Silence of the Lambs' and 'Dances with Wolves'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon bird made its debut in ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃâWalky Talky HawkyÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃÂ in 1946? Woody Woodpecker or Foghorn Leghorn?",
        "Answer": "Foghorn Leghorn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Of all the actors who played Doctor Who in the TV series of the same name, who appeared in the most episodes?",
        "Answer": "Tom Baker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the motel in which Janet Leigh's character is killed in 'Psycho'?",
        "Answer": "The Bates Motel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was Mel Gibson born?",
        "Answer": "USA"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Excluding animated TV shows, which 'B' was the first TV show to show a couple sharing a bed?",
        "Answer": "Bewitched"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Kate Hudson's character in the film 'Almost Famous' which is also the name of a famous song?",
        "Answer": "Penny Lane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Coronation Street begin ?",
        "Answer": "1960"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Dr Strangelove'?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the Sundance Kid in the 1969 film 'Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Redford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1986 film, set in Florence, was based on a novel by E. M. Forster?",
        "Answer": "'A Room With A View'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred in 'Dial M For Murder', 'Rear Window' and 'High Society'?",
        "Answer": "Grace Kelly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1999 TV series did Janet Street-Porter walk from Edinburgh to London? Capital Challenge, As The Crow Flies or Street Life?",
        "Answer": "As The Crow Flies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer starred in the film 'Desperately Seeking Susan'?",
        "Answer": "Madonna"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme for the Bond film 'From Russia With Love'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1974 film 'Zardoz', Sean Connery discovers that the name in the title of the film comes from which famous book?",
        "Answer": "The Wizard Of Oz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV show was set in Blair General Hospital?",
        "Answer": "Dr Kildare"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The second series of the TV comedy 'Blackadder' is set during the reign of which monarch?",
        "Answer": "Queen Elizabeth I"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first female monster to appear on the big screen?",
        "Answer": "The Bride Of Frankenstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the villain Max Shreck in the 1992 film 'Batman Returns'?",
        "Answer": "Christopher Walken"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The action at the end of the James Bond film 'A View To A Kill' features around which famous bridge?",
        "Answer": "Golden Gate Bridge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Not Known As Air' is an anagram of which comedy actor?",
        "Answer": "Rowan Atkinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedy duo had first names Bud and Lou?",
        "Answer": "Abbott and Costello"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did Daniel Day Lewis portray in the film 'In The Name Of The Father'?",
        "Answer": "Gerry Conlon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What character did actor Jerry Lacey play in the film 'Play It Again, Sam'?",
        "Answer": "Humphrey Bogart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress has played characters called Rose Loomis and Sugar Kane?",
        "Answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pop star has a daughter called Phoenix Chi Guizar?",
        "Answer": "Mel B"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the subject of Robert Altman's 1992 film 'The Player'? Hollywood, Baseball or the Stock Exchange?",
        "Answer": "Hollywood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the last living actor who was one of the magnificent Seven?",
        "Answer": "Robert Vaughan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Batman in the 1995 film 'Batman Forever'?",
        "Answer": "Val Kilmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1946 film took place in Bedford Falls?",
        "Answer": "'It's a wonderful life'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bill Pullman played the US President in what 1996 film?",
        "Answer": "'Independence Day'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Alfred Hitchcock's last film called?",
        "Answer": "'The Family Plot'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first film to feature the characters of Jay and Silent Bob?",
        "Answer": "Clerks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many 'Dirty Harry' films starred Clint Eastwood?",
        "Answer": "5 ('Dirty Harry', 'Magnum Force', 'The Enforcer', 'Sudden Impact' & 'The Dead Pool')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, who won BBC TVs 'Fame Academy'?",
        "Answer": "David Sneddon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The Cage' was the 1964 pilot episode of which TV series?",
        "Answer": "Star Trek"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous horror film featured a killer wearing a mask which was actually a Captain Kirk mask painted white?",
        "Answer": "Halloween"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1980 comedy features the character Ted Striker?",
        "Answer": "Airplane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the role of Dr. Malcom Crowe in the film 'The Sixth Sense'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Louise in the film 'Thelma and Louise'?",
        "Answer": "Susan Sarandon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1988 film does the character Archie Leach appear, and who plays him?",
        "Answer": "'A Fish Called Wanda', John Cleese."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the highest earning actor in America for the year 2000?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The title characters of which TV show live at Mockingbird Heights, 1313 Mockingbird Lane?",
        "Answer": "'The Munsters'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Cat Ballou in the 1965 film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Jane Fonda"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1985 thriller is a twisted character using a twisted blade revealed by a twisted character on his typewriter?",
        "Answer": "'Jagged Edge'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which war was taking place in the film 'Gone With The Wind'?",
        "Answer": "The Americal Civil War"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the second in Krzysztof Kieslowski's 'Three Colours' trilogy of films called? Red, White or Blue?",
        "Answer": "White"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What Bond villian has been played by Telly Savalas, Charles Gray and Donald Pleasance?",
        "Answer": "Blofeld"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series has characters called Reese, Dewey, Malcolm, Lois, Hal and Francis?",
        "Answer": "'Malcolm In The Middle'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who in real life has a father called Homer, a mother called Marge and sisters called Lisa and Maggie?",
        "Answer": "Matt Groening (creator of 'The Simpsons'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which long running television show originally featured as a series of 30 second features on 'The Tracey Ullman Show' in America in 1987?",
        "Answer": "'The Simpsons'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who supposed owned the car that Starsky and Hutch drove? Starsky, Hutch or Fossie Bear?",
        "Answer": "Starsky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who presented the TV program 'Ski Sunday' for 19 years?",
        "Answer": "David Vine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series was introduced by the music 'An Ordinary Copper'?",
        "Answer": "'Dixon Of Dock Green'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who or what was 'The Pink Panther' in the 1964 film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "A diamond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Deputy Marshal Samuel Gerard in the 1993 film 'The Fugitive'?",
        "Answer": "Tommy Lee Jones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you first have come across the character of Marty McFly?",
        "Answer": "'Back To The Future'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played Private James Francis Ryan in the film 'Saving Private Ryan'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Damon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Australian TV series, what type of animal was 'Skippy'?",
        "Answer": "Kangaroo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What kind of animal is the cartoon character Bullwinkle?",
        "Answer": "A moose"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many people does the Terminator played by Arnold Schwarzenegger kill in the film 'Terminator 2'?",
        "Answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The X-Files', what is Agent Mulder's first name?",
        "Answer": "Fox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which World Wrestling champion appeared in the films 'Rocky III', 'Mr. Nanny' and 'Muppets From Space'?",
        "Answer": "Hulk Hogan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first actor to play Doctor Who in the TV series of the same name?",
        "Answer": "'William Hartnell'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1954 Alfred Hitchcock film was remade in 1998 as 'A Perfect Murder'?",
        "Answer": "'Dial M For Murder'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1959 film made won 11 Oscars?",
        "Answer": "Ben Hur"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'NCC 1701' is the registration number of which famous fictional vehicle?",
        "Answer": "The Starship Enterprise"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Jungle Book' what type of animal was Bagheera?",
        "Answer": "A panther"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Lester Burnham is a character in which 1999 film?",
        "Answer": "American Beauty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film star did Martin Landau play in the 1994 film 'Ed Wood'?",
        "Answer": "Bela Lugosi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which fictional character has been played on screen by Julie Newmar, Ertha Kitt and Michelle Pfeiffer?",
        "Answer": "Catwoman (from 'Batman')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the character who was 'Sleepless In Seattle'?",
        "Answer": "Tom Hanks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With whom do Alan Titchmarsh and Charlie Dimmock join forces to form the Ground Force?",
        "Answer": "Tommy Walsh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Phoebe's twin sister in the TV show 'Friends'? Lucia, Marcela or Ursula?",
        "Answer": "Ursula"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Casablanca' is set around which war?",
        "Answer": "World War II"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1942 film features the characters Rick, Isla and Laszlo?",
        "Answer": "'Casablanca'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1992 Belgian film features a documentary crew filming the activities of a serial killer?",
        "Answer": "'Man Bites Dog'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did George Lazenby play James Bond?",
        "Answer": "'On her majesty's secret service'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which 1968 sci-fi film did the band Duran Duran get their name?",
        "Answer": "'Barbarella'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of He Man's arch enemy?",
        "Answer": "Skeletor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played 'The Bionic Woman'?",
        "Answer": "Lindsay Wagner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many of the seven dwarfs wore glasses?",
        "Answer": "One (Doc)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Bruce Willis' character in 'Die Hard'?",
        "Answer": "John McClane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Jessica Tandy won the best Actress Oscar in 1989 for which film?",
        "Answer": "'Driving Miss Daisy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Inspector Morse's Christian name?",
        "Answer": "Endeavour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1974 film 'Chinatown'?",
        "Answer": "Roman Polanski"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Mickey Mouse make his debut as 'Steamboat Willie'? 1928, 1931 or 1934?",
        "Answer": "1928"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Deckard is the main character in what 1982 film?",
        "Answer": "Blade Runner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which movie did Clark Gable win his only acting Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'It Happened One Night'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1988 Penny Marshall became the first female director to have a film take more than 100 million dollars at the box office. What was the film?",
        "Answer": "'Big'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film originally starring Audrey Hepburn in the title role, was remade in 1995 with Julia Ormond in the same role?",
        "Answer": "'Sabrina'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British playwright wrote Boys From The Blackstuff?",
        "Answer": "Alan Bleasdale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Edina's son in the TV comedy series 'Absolutely Fabulous'?",
        "Answer": "Serge"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV family live at 742 Evergreen Terrace?",
        "Answer": "The Simpsons"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was 'Rover' the patroller in the TV show 'The Prisoner'?",
        "Answer": "A balloon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 2002 film 'Road To Perdition'?",
        "Answer": "Sam Mendes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which US TV show featured a stuntman with side-kicks Jody and Howie?",
        "Answer": "'The Fall Guy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bonnie Langford played assistant to which two actors in the TV series 'Doctor Who'?",
        "Answer": "Colin Baker and Sylvester McCoy."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1999, what film became Tom Hanks first sequel?",
        "Answer": "'Toy Story 2'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred as Jim Hacker in 'Yes, Minister'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Eddington"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV cast had a hit with 'Hi-Fidelity'?",
        "Answer": "'The Kids From Fame'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Alien'?",
        "Answer": "Ridley Scott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1995 film features the line 'Every man dies, not every man really lives.'?",
        "Answer": "'Braveheart'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1993 film does the character Dr Richard Kimble appear?",
        "Answer": "'The Fugitive'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 2001 film 'Mulholland Dr.'?",
        "Answer": "David Lynch"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the murder victim at the beginning of the TV series 'Twin Peaks'?",
        "Answer": "Laura Palmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character played by Donald Sutherland in the 1975 film 'The Day Of The Locust' which is also the name of a famous cartoon character?",
        "Answer": "Homer Simpson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1960 film was written by Arthur Miller and starred his wife Marilyn Monroe?",
        "Answer": "'The Misfits'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'The Heat Is On' by Glen Frey feature on the soundtrack to what 1984 film?",
        "Answer": "Beverly Hills Cop"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In cinema, what came first - sound or colour?",
        "Answer": "Colour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The path of the righteous manÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬ÃÂ¦' quote from the film 'Pulp Fiction' comes from which book of the Bible?",
        "Answer": "Ezekiel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was actor Russell Crowe born?",
        "Answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 2001 film was based on a 1969 short story by Brian Aldiss called 'Super Toys Last All Summer'?",
        "Answer": "'A.I.'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many different roles does Alec Guinness play in 'Kind Hearts And Coronets'?",
        "Answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what two films does Paul Newman play the character of Fast Eddie Felson?",
        "Answer": "'The Hustler' and 'The Color Of Money'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress said 'When I'm good I'm very good, but when I'm bad I'm better'?",
        "Answer": "Mae West"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Bond film does James Bond get married and what was the name of his wife?",
        "Answer": "'On Her Majesty's Secret Service', Tracy (Draco)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the family name of the family portrayed in the Godfather films?",
        "Answer": "Corleone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you find Hatchet Harry and Barry The Baptist?",
        "Answer": "Lock, Stock And Two Smoking Barrels"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film features the characters of Raymond and Charlie Babbitt?",
        "Answer": "'Rain Man'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which British TV series were David Jason and Gwen Taylor married?",
        "Answer": "'A Bit Of A Do'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many Oscars did the 1993 film SchindlerÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s List receive?",
        "Answer": "7"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor, whose father is also an actor, took over from Michael Praed playing Robin Hood on TV?",
        "Answer": "Jason Connery"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who presented the childrens TV show 'Animal Magic' from 1962 to 1983?",
        "Answer": "Johnny Morris"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was the first to use Dolby surround sound?",
        "Answer": "'Star Wars'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Steamboat Willy' introduces which character into TV and films?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor's first name means 'cool breeze over the mountains' in the Hawaiian language?",
        "Answer": "Keanu Reeves"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Rita's tutor in the film 'Educating Rita'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Caine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actor Richard Kiel is best known for playing the same character in two different films. What is the name of this character?",
        "Answer": "'Jaws' (in two James Bond films)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Pierce Brosnan play James Bond for the first time?",
        "Answer": "'Goldeneye'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does Kevin Costner star as Jim Garrison?",
        "Answer": "'J.F.K.'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Oskar Schindler in the film 'Schindler's List'?",
        "Answer": "Liam Neeson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor won his first best actor Oscar for the 1986 film 'The Color Of Money'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Newman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'Moon River' appeared in what 1961 film?",
        "Answer": "'Breakfast At Tiffany's'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Are You Being Served?' what is the name of the department store?",
        "Answer": "Grace Brothers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'Men Behaving Badly', what was the name of Gary's other flatmate before Tony moved in?",
        "Answer": "Dermot"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Dr Who, what does the acronym TARDIS stand for?",
        "Answer": "Time And Relative Dimensions in Space"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who supplied the voice of the genie in the 1992 film 'Aladdin'?",
        "Answer": "Robin Williams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name was actor Arthur Stanley Jefferson better known?",
        "Answer": "Stan Laurel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which real-life brothers starred opposite Michelle Pfeiffer in the 1989 film 'The Fabulous Baker Boys'?",
        "Answer": "Jeff and Beau Bridges"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first non-human to win an Oscar?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which animated character from TV and films, was originally named from a nonsense phrase in Frank Sinatra's 'Strangers In The Night'?",
        "Answer": "Scooby Doo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American film features a villain called John Doe and a police officers called William Somerset and David Mills?",
        "Answer": "'Se7en'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1999 film does the main character quit his job at Media Monthly Magazine to start work at fast food joint Mr. Smiley's?",
        "Answer": "'American Beauty'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon show included characters called Thelma and Shaggy?",
        "Answer": "Scooby Doo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does BAFTA stand for?",
        "Answer": "British Academy of Film and Television Arts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress won three BAFTAs in the 1990s for playing a policewoman on TV?",
        "Answer": "Helen Mirren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Whoopi Goldberg win an Oscar playing the character of Oda May?",
        "Answer": "'Ghost'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which children's TV show might you find Mrs Goggins?",
        "Answer": "Postman Pat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Before becoming a pop star, Lisa Stansfield was a presenter on which British music show?",
        "Answer": "'Razzamatazz'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was author Ian Fleming's original choice to play James Bond on film, but who couldn't do it as he was already comitted to a TV series?",
        "Answer": "Roger Moore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What TV programme is shown in France as 'Aux Frontieres du Reel'?",
        "Answer": "The X-Files (it translates as 'At the borders of reality')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1986 film 'Stand By Me'? Rob Reiner or Robert Zemeckis?",
        "Answer": "Rob Reiner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When appearing in the credits at the end of a film, who is Alan Smithee?",
        "Answer": "An alias for the director, who disowned the film and didn't want to use his own name."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer played Billie Holiday in the 1972 film 'Lady Sings The Blues'?",
        "Answer": "Diana Ross"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film had a funeral sequence featuring approximately 300,000 extras?",
        "Answer": "Gandhi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Homer's boss in the TV show 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Montgomery Burns"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 1971 TV movie 'Duel' was one of the first pieces of work by which famous film director?",
        "Answer": "Steven Spielberg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Walt Disney's first feature length cartoon?",
        "Answer": "'Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did 'Eastenders' first appear on British television?",
        "Answer": "1985"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character had an arch enemy called Baron Silas Greenback?",
        "Answer": "Dangermouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the final film in Krzysztof Kieslowski's 'Three Colours' trilogy? Red, White or Blue?",
        "Answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female actress starred alongside Tom Cruise in the film 'Top Gun'?",
        "Answer": "Kelly McGillis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer/songwriter played the character of Renfield in the 1994 film 'Bram Stoker's Dracula'?",
        "Answer": "Tom Waits"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the TV show 'Queenie's Castle'?",
        "Answer": "Diana Dors"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the butler in 'The Addams family'?",
        "Answer": "Lurch"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the sequel to the 1982 film 'Conan The Barbarian' called?",
        "Answer": "'Conan The Destroyer'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Magic Roundabout' what type of animal was Brian?",
        "Answer": "A snail"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor from the TV show 'Friends' also appeared in the film 'Lost In Space'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Le Blanc"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Agent Scully in the X-Files?",
        "Answer": "Gillian Anderson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not appear in the film 'Wild At Heart'? Kyle Maclachlan, Sherilyn Fenn or Willem Dafoe?",
        "Answer": "Kyle Maclachlan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which director's first film was called 'THX 1138'?",
        "Answer": "George Lucas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What western won the best picture Oscar in 1993?",
        "Answer": "Unforgiven"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the only silent film to win the Best Picture award at the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'Wings'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the character of Jack Sommersby in a 1993 film?",
        "Answer": "Richard Gere"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American film director said 'When I grow up I still want to be a director' in Time magazine in 1985?",
        "Answer": "Steven Spielberg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Walt Disney film 'Snow White And The Seven Dwarfs', what were the names of the seven dwarfs?",
        "Answer": "Doc, Sneezy, Grumpy, Happy, Sleepy, Dopey and Bashful."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Robert De Niro played Max Cady in the Martin Scorcese film 'Cape Fear', but who played him in the 1962 version of the same film?",
        "Answer": "Robert Mitchum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose last film as a director was 'Family Plot'?",
        "Answer": "Alfred Hitchcock"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is the 1991 film 'Raise The Red Lantern' set?",
        "Answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film features the characters of Raymond and Charlie Babbitt?",
        "Answer": "Rain Man"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As Dorothy taps her heels together 3 times and prepares to return to Kansas at the end of 'The Wizard of Oz' what does she repeatedly say?",
        "Answer": "'There's no place like home'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the first names of 'Starsky and Hutch'?",
        "Answer": "Dave and Ken"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The first interracial kiss on American TV involved which two Star Trek characters?",
        "Answer": "Lt Uhura and Capt Kirk"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the profession of Mastermind winner Fred Housego?",
        "Answer": "Taxi Driver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the local pub in the TV series 'Only Fools and Horses'?",
        "Answer": "The Nag's Head"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The title character of which TV show read a newspaper called 'The Village'?",
        "Answer": "'The Prisoner'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sheriff Coltraine in the 'Dukes of Hazzard' had a dog called what? Mazzy, Buck or Flash?",
        "Answer": "Flash"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film features the famous scene of Marilyn Monroe's dress blowing as she stands over a subway grate?",
        "Answer": "'The Seven Year Itch'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Carlito's Way', who played Carlito?",
        "Answer": "Al Pacino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which US TV and film detective has famously never revealed his first name?",
        "Answer": "Columbo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Disney's 'The Incredible Journey' what type of animal was 'Badger'?",
        "Answer": "A dog (bull-terrier)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bono from the band U2 paid over $50,000 dollars in 1994 for a suit worn by who in a 1940 film?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of monsters are at the centre of the films 'The Howling' and 'Ginger Snaps'?",
        "Answer": "Werewolves"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name was the British film actor Sir Charles Spencer better known?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If Paul Michael Glazer and David Soul played 'Starsky and Hutch', who did Antonio Fargas play?",
        "Answer": "Huggie Bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who made their directorial debut with the 1991 film 'Little Man Tate'?",
        "Answer": "Jodie Foster"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Gissa Job' was the catchphrase of which character from the TV show 'Boys from the black stuff'?",
        "Answer": "Yosser Hughes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Patrick Trench in 'One Foot In The Grave'?",
        "Answer": "Angus Deayton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Beth Jordache in the TV soap opera 'Brookside'?",
        "Answer": "Anna Friel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who wrote, directed and starred in the 1996 film 'Sling Blade'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Bob Thornton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Maverick, Goose, and Iceman are characters in which 1986 film?",
        "Answer": "'Top Gun'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Patsy's surname in the TV show 'Absolutely Fabulous'?",
        "Answer": "Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Tim Allen provided the voice for which computer generated character in a 1995 film?",
        "Answer": "'Buzz Lightyear' (in 'Toy Story')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1983 film 'Christine', who or what was Christine?",
        "Answer": "A car (with demonic powers)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film directed by Richard Joffe was the only British film to win the Palme D'Or award at the Cannes film festival in the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "'The Mission'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor is the narrator in the film 'Blade Runner'?",
        "Answer": "Harrison Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What song played on the Levis commercial featuring Eddie Kidd?",
        "Answer": "'When A Man Loves A Woman' (by Percy Sledge)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor anonymously entered a look-alike contest for himself in Monaco, and came third?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which alcoholic drink was advertised on TV by Joan Collins and Leonard Rossiter?",
        "Answer": "Cinzano"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Finding Nemo' what is the name of Nemo's dad who is looking for him?",
        "Answer": "Marlin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon superhero had his base in a postbox in Baker Street?",
        "Answer": "Dangermouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actor Hugh Grant graduated from which University with a degree in English?",
        "Answer": "Oxford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two TV actors provided the voices for the cartoon character Dangermouse and his side-kick Penfold?",
        "Answer": "David Jason and Terry Scott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Catwoman in the 1992 film 'Batman Returns'?",
        "Answer": "Michelle Pfieffer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Quentin Tarantino film was an adaptation of Elmore Leonard's novel called 'Rum Punch'?",
        "Answer": "'Jackie Brown'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: Mickey Mouse made his on-screen debut in the same cartoon as Minnie Mouse made hers?",
        "Answer": "True (in the silent cartoon 'Plane Crazy')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played 'Nice Guy Eddie' in Quentin Tarantino's 'Reservoir Dogs'?",
        "Answer": "Chris Penn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Judith Keppel the first person to do on British television?",
        "Answer": "Win a million pounds (on 'Who Wants To Be A Millionaire')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the 1960 film 'Spartacus'?",
        "Answer": "Kirk Douglas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actress appeared as the first Playboy centerfold in 1953?",
        "Answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Dorothy's surname in 'The Wizard Of Oz'?",
        "Answer": "Gale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Eastenders character married Cat Slater on Christmas day 2003?",
        "Answer": "Alfie Moon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What kind of animal is James Stewart's invisible friend in the film 'Harvey'?",
        "Answer": "A rabbit."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Roger Moore play James Bond for the first time?",
        "Answer": "'Live and let die'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two brothers play the title roles in 'The Fabulous Baker Boys'?",
        "Answer": "Jeff Bridges and Beau Bridges."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the title role in the Alfred Hitchcock film 'Marnie'?",
        "Answer": "Tippi Hedren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2001, what is the highest grossing film of all time?",
        "Answer": "'Titanic'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1992 Robert Altman film featured cameos from Angelica Huston, Burt Reynolds and Cher, all playing themselves?",
        "Answer": "The Player"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Bugs Bunny's catchphrase?",
        "Answer": "'What's Up Doc'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which sport is the 1988 film 'Bull Durham' centered around?",
        "Answer": "Baseball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1963 film features 'The Cooler King', 'The Scrounger', 'The Forger' and 'Big X'?",
        "Answer": "'The Great Escape'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who produced, directed and starred in 'Citizen Kane'?",
        "Answer": "Orson Welles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor and actress played the leading roles in the TV series 'Moonlighting'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis and Cybil Shepard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Tom Cruise play Ron Kovic?",
        "Answer": "'Born on the 4th of July'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many best director Oscars did Stanley Kubrick win?",
        "Answer": "None"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Absolutely Fabulous', who played Edina's mother?",
        "Answer": "June Whitfield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the sitcom 'Are You Being Served', what was the name of the character who had the catchphrase 'I'm Free'?",
        "Answer": "Mr Humphries"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose acceptance speech at the Oscars in 2001 included the line 'I love the world, I'm so happy, thank you'?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1980s film did Dudley Moore play an elf?",
        "Answer": "'Santa Claus The Movie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film and TV series, what does the letter 'M' stand for in 'M*A*S*H'?",
        "Answer": "Mobile"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Clarice Starling is a character in what 1991 film?",
        "Answer": "'Silence of the lambs'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor has played the characters Fletcher Reed, Lloyd Christmas and The Riddler on screen?",
        "Answer": "Jim Carrey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first African-American to win the best actress award at the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "Halle Berry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The actor Brandon Lee died during an accident on the set of what film?",
        "Answer": "'The Crow'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did the character Ellen Ripley first appear?",
        "Answer": "Alien"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British band have had hit albums called 'Gold Mother', 'Seven' and 'Laid'?",
        "Answer": "James"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980 film features Bill Murray battling against a gopher?",
        "Answer": "Caddyshack"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What film's theme song did Ray Parker Junior sing in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Ghostbusters"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which piece of film memorabilia from the film 'The Wizard Of Oz' made 666,000 dollars when auctioned in 2000?",
        "Answer": "The slippers worn by Judy Garland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film won the best picture, best director, best actor and best actress Oscars in 1992?",
        "Answer": "Silence of the lambs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1976 film features the characters of Fat Sam and Dandy Dan?",
        "Answer": "'Bugsy Malone'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Stuart, in the 1999 film 'Stuart Little'?",
        "Answer": "Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On TV, how are Simon Shelton, John Simmit, Nikky Smedley and Pui Fan Lee better known?",
        "Answer": "The Teletubbies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the surname of the family in the TV series '2 point 4 children'?",
        "Answer": "Porter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played Ronnie in the film 'Close Encounters Of The Third Kind'?",
        "Answer": "Terri Garr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at 2003, other than Tom Hanks, who is the only actor who has won back to back Best Actor Oscars?",
        "Answer": "Spencer Tracy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actors Warren Beatty and Annette Bening married after meeting on the set of what film?",
        "Answer": "'Bugsy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Elizabeth Taylor shoot to fame as a child star in 1944?",
        "Answer": "'National Velvet'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon takes place in Greendale in Cumbria?",
        "Answer": "Postman Pat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 'Rocky' films, what was the first name of Rocky's wife?",
        "Answer": "Adrian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Heather, Joshua and Michael were the three main characters in which 1999 film?",
        "Answer": "'The Blair Witch Project'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality is comedian Steve Coogan's character Tony Ferrino?",
        "Answer": "Portuguese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film was the character of Marion Crane famously killed?",
        "Answer": "Psycho"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed 'The Godfather'?",
        "Answer": "Francis Ford Copolla"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy series 'Frasier', what is Frasier's surname?",
        "Answer": "Crane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British film director once said 'Actors should be treated like cattle'?",
        "Answer": "Alfred Hitchcock"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 2000 film features a psychopath called Patrick Bateman?",
        "Answer": "'American Psycho'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two contestants from Channel 4's first 'Big Brother' series had a baby in 2001?",
        "Answer": "Claire and Tom"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Mary in the film 'There's Something About Mary'?",
        "Answer": "Cameron Diaz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1995 film featuring talking animals is based on a book by Dick King-Smith?",
        "Answer": "Babe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Eye Of The Tiger' by Survivor was the theme song to which film?",
        "Answer": "'Rocky III'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor directed the film 'A River Runs Through It'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Redford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where was the TV series 'Starsky and Hutch' based? San Francisco, Los Angeles or New York?",
        "Answer": "Los Angeles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who created the muppets?",
        "Answer": "Jim Henson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the adult version of the TV show 'TISWAS'? 'O.T.T.', 'A.P.B.' or 'S.F.A.'?",
        "Answer": "O.T.T."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the 1975 film 'Tommy'?",
        "Answer": "Roger Daltrey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Jennifer Warnes had two number one hit singles with duets from which two films?",
        "Answer": "'Dirty Dancing', 'An Officer And A Gentleman'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1975 film features the characters of Riff Raff, Magenta and Doctor Frank-n-Furter?",
        "Answer": "'The Rocky Horror Picture Show'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played Princess Leia in the film 'Star Wars'?",
        "Answer": "Carrie Fisher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous musician narrated the adventures of Thomas the Tank Engine on British television?",
        "Answer": "Ringo Starr"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Elvis Presley make his acting debut?",
        "Answer": "'Love Me Tender'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Rachel's surname in 'Friends'?",
        "Answer": "Greene"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Marlon Brando won best actor award for what 1954 film?",
        "Answer": "'On the waterfront'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What cartoon characters are described as being 'three apples high'?",
        "Answer": "Smurfs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the English translation of the film title 'Il Buono, Il Brutto, Il Cattivo'?",
        "Answer": "The Good, The Bad and The Ugly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Bicentennial Man' starring Robin Williams was based on a story by which author?",
        "Answer": "Isaac Asimov"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress plays Kevin Spacey's wife in the film 'American Beauty'?",
        "Answer": "Annette Bening"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress is the subject of Terry Johnson's play 'Insignificance'?",
        "Answer": "Marilyn Monroe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Aliens'?",
        "Answer": "James Cameron"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Archibald Leach is the real name of which actor?",
        "Answer": "Cary Grant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What film, directed by Alfred Hitchcock, included a dream sequence designed by Salvador Dali?",
        "Answer": "'Spellbound'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who stars as Roy Neary in the film 'Close Encounters Of The Third Kind'?",
        "Answer": "Richard Dreyfuss"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1974 disaster movie starred Steve McQueen, Paul Newman and Faye Dunaway?",
        "Answer": "'The Towering Inferno'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1973 film 'American Graffiti'?",
        "Answer": "George Lucas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Life Of Brian', who played Brian?",
        "Answer": "Graham Chapman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Only Fools And Horses', what is the name of Boycie's wife?",
        "Answer": "Marlene"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Truman's first name in the film 'The Truman Show'?",
        "Answer": "Truman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons' who runs the store called the Leftorium?",
        "Answer": "Ned Flanders"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Che Guevera alongside Madonna in the film 'Evita'?",
        "Answer": "Antonia Banderas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Better known in the world of music, who played the leading role in the film 'Buster'?",
        "Answer": "Phil Collins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the leading characters Rhett Butler and Scarlett O'Hara in the film 'Gone With The Wind'?",
        "Answer": "Clark Gable and Vivien Leigh."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Philip Marlowe in the 1946 film 'The Big Sleep'?",
        "Answer": "Humphrey Bogart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was the subject of the book 'The Moon's A Balloon'?",
        "Answer": "David Niven"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the films 'Marathon Man' and 'Midnight Cowboy'?",
        "Answer": "John Schlesinger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Carrie in the TV series 'Sex and the city'?",
        "Answer": "Sarah Jessica Parker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV comedy series sometimes featured a policeman called Roy Slater?",
        "Answer": "'Only Fools And Horses'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1967 film, was Lee Van Cleef ' The Good', 'The Bad' or 'The Ugly'?",
        "Answer": "'The Bad'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1988 film would you find a villain called Hans Gruber?",
        "Answer": "'Die Hard'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of toy animal was 'wheezy' in the film 'Toy Story 2'?",
        "Answer": "Penguin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Clint Eastwood play Dirty Harry for the second time?",
        "Answer": "'Magnum Force'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the film 'Gandhi'?",
        "Answer": "Ben Kingsley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Basil's wife in 'Fawlty Towers'?",
        "Answer": "Sybil"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animals were the subject of the 2002 film 'Eight Legged Freaks'?",
        "Answer": "Spiders"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Poison Ivy in the 1997 film 'Batman and Robin'?",
        "Answer": "Uma Thurman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Superman's name on Krypton? Kal-El, Ke-Tol or Kon-Tal?",
        "Answer": "Kal-El"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which city's police department does Columbo work for in the American TV show?",
        "Answer": "Los Angeles'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character played by Ed Harris in 'The Truman Show'? Christof, Kramen or Hristo?",
        "Answer": "Christof"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Tom Hanks won the best actor Oscar in 1995 for his performance in what film?",
        "Answer": "Forrest Gump"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character was featured in the short film 'Steamboat Willie'?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what film did Julia Roberts first receive a best actress nomination at the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'Pretty Woman'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Bond film was chosen as the follow up to 'Dr No' after John F Kennedy listed it as one of his favourite books?",
        "Answer": "'From Russia With Love'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1965 film included the songs 'Do Re Mi', 'Climb Every Mountain' and 'Edelweiss'?",
        "Answer": "'The Sound Of Music'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cult film was based on the Novel 'Do Androids Dream of  Electric Sheep'?",
        "Answer": "Blade Runner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What actress was the subject of the 1983 film 'Mommie Dearest'?",
        "Answer": "Joan Crawford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which BBC TV show would you associate the character of David Brent?",
        "Answer": "'The Office'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who provided the voice of the title character in the 2001 film 'Shrek''?",
        "Answer": "Mike Myers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian's real name is Jim Moir?",
        "Answer": "Vic Reeves"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Starring in the film 'Thje Sheikh', who was known as the big screen's first great lover?",
        "Answer": "Rudolph Valentino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character had wings which were like 'a shield of steel'?",
        "Answer": "Batfink"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which James Bond film did the Indian tennis player, Vijay Amritraj appear?",
        "Answer": "'Octopussy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the names of the four teletubbies?",
        "Answer": "Po, La-la, Dipsey and Tinky-Winky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 2001 film 'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone'?",
        "Answer": "Chris Columbus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "If you live in Albert Square in the TV show 'Eastenders', what would the first three digits of your postcode be?",
        "Answer": "E20"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which band released the single 'Hooligan' in 1999?",
        "Answer": "Embrace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV show would you find the character of Edina Monsoon?",
        "Answer": "'Absolutely Fabulous'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title roles in the TV series 'Sapphire and Steel'?",
        "Answer": "David McCallum and Joanna Lumley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Lex Luthor in the Superman films?",
        "Answer": "Gene Hackman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British comdey series featured characters including Bob Fleming, Colin Hunt and Dave Angel?",
        "Answer": "'The Fast Show'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Norman Bates in the 1960 film 'Psycho'?",
        "Answer": "Anthony Perkins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Bodie's partner in the TV series 'The Professionals'?",
        "Answer": "Doyle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV sitcom 'Friends', where does Joey keep his favourite book?",
        "Answer": "In the freezer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the animated film 'Jungle Book', what were the names of the four vultures?",
        "Answer": "John, Paul, George and Ringo."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city was actor Russell Crowe born?",
        "Answer": "Wellington, New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At what event was Helen Adams runner-up in July, 2001?",
        "Answer": "The TV program 'Big Brother'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the tortoise in the TV show 'The Flowerpot Men' called?",
        "Answer": "Slowcoach"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous American singer got a Best Supporting Actor Nomination for the movie 'From Here to Eternity'?",
        "Answer": "Frank Sinatra"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedienne is married to Geoffrey Durham?",
        "Answer": "Victoria Wood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1961 film did Jackie Gleason play Minnesota Fats?",
        "Answer": "'The Hustler'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is film star Warren Beatty's famous sister?",
        "Answer": "Shirley Maclaine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is the film 'Jean De Florette' set?",
        "Answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor had the real name of Marion Morrison?",
        "Answer": "John Wayne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The Evening Star' was the sequel to which 1983 Oscar winning film?",
        "Answer": "'Terms Of Endearment'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the two main stars of the film 'Nine and a half weeks'?",
        "Answer": "Mickery Rourke and Kim Basinger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2001, what 5 James Bond films have titles with only one word?",
        "Answer": "'Goldfinger', 'Thunderball', 'Moonraker', 'Octopussy' and 'Goldeneye'."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Walt Disney's first animated film with sound called?",
        "Answer": "'Steamboat Willie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress from the TV show 'Friends' once appeared in the video for Bruce Springsteen's 'Dancing In The Dark'?",
        "Answer": "Courtney Cox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the pilot of Thunderbird 2?",
        "Answer": "Virgil"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Barbara Good in 'The Good Life' ?",
        "Answer": "Felicity Kendall"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Italian word for 'pine eye' is also the name of which famous film?",
        "Answer": "'Pinocchio'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1995 film 'Heat' starring Robert De Niro and Al Pacino?",
        "Answer": "Michael Mann"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which two films does Kurt Russell play the character of Snake Plissken?",
        "Answer": "'Escape From New York' and 'Escape From L.A.'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Bambi's friend, Thumper?",
        "Answer": "A rabbit."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Frankie in the 1991 film 'Frankie and Johnny'?",
        "Answer": "Michelle Pfeiffer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Wizard Of Oz', what was the Tin Man looking for?",
        "Answer": "A heart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Chief Martin Brody in the film 'Jaws'?",
        "Answer": "Roy Scheider"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character was played by Laurence Olivier in a 1954 film and Ian McKellen in a 1995 film?",
        "Answer": "Richard III"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon characters live at 39 Canyon Way?",
        "Answer": "The Flintstones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the registration plate on Lady Penelope's pink car in 'Thunderbirds'?",
        "Answer": "FAB 1"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1991, Anthony Hopkins won the best actor Oscar for his performance in what film?",
        "Answer": "'Silence Of The Lambs'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'The Eiger Sanction'?",
        "Answer": "Clint Eastwood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which childrens TV series is set in Pontypandy?",
        "Answer": "Fireman Sam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor played the Mock Turtle in the 1933 film 'Alice In Wonderland'?",
        "Answer": "Cary Grant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the names of the four Marx brothers?",
        "Answer": "Groucho, Zeppo, Chico and Harpo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the first married couple to guest star in an episode of 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Paul and Linda McCartney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which quiz show often featured the line 'I've started so I'll finish'?",
        "Answer": "Mastermind"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of dog was the cartoon character Snoopy?",
        "Answer": "A beagle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1976 film featured Robert De Niro, Harvey Keitel and Jodie Foster?",
        "Answer": "'Taxi Driver'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what nickname was the TV character Benjamin Franklin Pierce known?",
        "Answer": "Hawkeye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the profession of Charles Foster Kane in the film 'Citizen Kane'?",
        "Answer": "Newspaper owner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of actress Melanie Griffiths' mother, who appeared in the Alfred Hitchcock film 'The Birds'?",
        "Answer": "Tippi Hedren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British TV series takes place in Sun Hill?",
        "Answer": "'The Bill'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1984 film did Sean Connery return as James Bond?",
        "Answer": "'Never Say Never Again'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film and TV series, what does the letter 'A' stand for in 'M*A*S*H'?",
        "Answer": "Army"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played the title role in the TV series 'Foxy Lady'?",
        "Answer": "Diane Keen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Alfred Hitchcock film features a wheelchair bound James Stewart convinced that a neighbour has committed murder?",
        "Answer": "'Rear Window'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer played the character of Ophelia in the 1969 film 'Hamlet'?",
        "Answer": "Marianne Faithfull"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1961, which actress became the first to win an Oscar for acting in a non-English film?",
        "Answer": "Sophia Loren"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you find 'the Knights who say Ni'?",
        "Answer": "'Monty Python and the Holy Grail'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does the character Travis Bickle appear?",
        "Answer": "'Taxi Driver'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour are the spots on Mr Blobby?",
        "Answer": "Yellow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does the character Pussy Galore appear?",
        "Answer": "'Goldfinger'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series first shown in 1996 and 1997 featured characters called Warren, Milly, Miles, Anna and Egg?",
        "Answer": "'This Life'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is the 2000 film 'Amores Perros' set?",
        "Answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which TV show was the cartoon show 'Top Cat' based?",
        "Answer": "'Sergeant Bilko'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The main characters on what science fiction TV series met while working together on the 'Star Bright Project'?",
        "Answer": "'Quantum Leap'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What rank did the leader of the TV series 'The A-Team' reach in the army?",
        "Answer": "Colonel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress wrote the 1987 autobiography 'This 'n that'?",
        "Answer": "Bette Davis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Eastenders', Tiffany was knocked down and killed by which character?",
        "Answer": "Frank Butcher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors play the title roles in 'Dumb and Dumber'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actress was only 3 years old when she appeared in the film 'The Red-Haired Alibi'?",
        "Answer": "Shirley Temple"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Basil Rathbone makes his first appearance as Sherlock Holmes?",
        "Answer": "'The Hound Of The Baskervilles'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Bob the Builder's girlfriend called?",
        "Answer": "Wendy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress, also known for her singing, played the character Alexandra Medford in the film 'The Witches of Eastwick'?",
        "Answer": "Cher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Before finding fame as a film director, who played an Elvis impersonator in the last episode of 'The Golden Girls'?",
        "Answer": "Quentin Tarantino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the male and female leads in the 1992 film 'Far and Away'?",
        "Answer": "Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How are the employees of the Charles Townsend Associates private detective agency better known?",
        "Answer": "'Charlie's Angels'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which James Bond film does the character Dr Christmas Jones feature?",
        "Answer": "'The World Is Not Enough'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 2000 film would you find the character of General Maximus Decimus Meridus?",
        "Answer": "Gladiator"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress won an Oscar playing the lead role in the 1969 film 'The Prime Of Miss Jean Brodie'?",
        "Answer": "Maggie Smith"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'A Kind Of Magic' and 'Hammer To Fall' by Queen are songs on the soundtrack to which 1986 film?",
        "Answer": "'Highlander'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1984 film about the life of a famous composer, won an Oscar for best film?",
        "Answer": "'Amadeus'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which TV game show have Stephen Fry, Magnus Magnusson, Michael Parkinson and Gabby Yorath all made guest appearances?",
        "Answer": "'Countdown'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What product was the first to be advertised on the UK's Channel 5?",
        "Answer": "Chanel No. 5"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1974 sequel won six Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'The Godfather: Part II'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Toy Story 2', who provided the voice of Jesse the cow-girl?",
        "Answer": "Joan Cusack"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first name of the character played by Kelly McDonald in the film 'Trainspotting'?",
        "Answer": "Diane"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Tom Hanks star as a boy in a adult body?",
        "Answer": "Big"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Ivor The Engine', what was the name of the dragon?",
        "Answer": "Idris"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which action packed TV show won best drama award at the Emmys in 1966 and 1967?",
        "Answer": "Mission Impossible"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Dooley Wilson is famous for playing what piano playing character on film?",
        "Answer": "Sam (in 'Casablanca')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Miss Jones in the TV show 'Rising Damp'?",
        "Answer": "Frances de la Tour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous Hollywood actor (not including Presidents) had the highest military rank as a Brigadier General in the US Army Reserve?",
        "Answer": "James Stewart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Two different actors have won Oscars playing the character of Vito Corleone in two different Godfather films. Who are these two actors?",
        "Answer": "Marlon Brando (in 'The Godfather') and Robert De Niro (in 'The Godfather Part II')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade was the film 'The Exorcist' originally released?",
        "Answer": "1970s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Lion King' character did Jeremy Irons provide the voice for?",
        "Answer": "Scar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Musky Muskrat was the side kick of which cartoon lawman?",
        "Answer": "Deputy Dawg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, who was the first person to be voted out of the second 'Celebrity Big Brother'?",
        "Answer": "Goldie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film starring Mel Gibson opens with the song 'Jingle Bell Rock'?",
        "Answer": "'Lethal Weapon'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which England based animation studio received 6 consecutive Oscar nominations for Best Short Animated Film?",
        "Answer": "Aardman Animation"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1950 movie 'Harvey', what type of animal was Harvey?",
        "Answer": "Rabbit"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 2001 film 'The Royal Tenenbaums'? Luke Wilson, Owen Wilson or Wes Anderson?",
        "Answer": "Wes Anderson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred in the films 'Addicted To Love', 'City Of Angels' and 'Courage Under Fire'?",
        "Answer": "Meg Ryan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first movie with audible dialogue?",
        "Answer": "'The Jazz Singer'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first female monster to appear on film?",
        "Answer": "The bride of Frankenstein."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which Bond film does the character of Q appear for the first time?",
        "Answer": "'From Russia With Love'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour was Captain Kirk's seat on the Starship Enterprise?",
        "Answer": "Black"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'S' was the name of Nicole Kidman's character in the 2001 film 'Moulin Rouge'?",
        "Answer": "Satine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Alf Garnett in the TV series 'Till Death Do Us Part'?",
        "Answer": "Warren Mitchell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which television show took place at Wentworth Detention Centre?",
        "Answer": "'Prisoner: Cell Block H'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won the best actress Oscar for the film 'Driving Miss Daisy'?",
        "Answer": "Jessica Tandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the two main characters in the film 'Dirty Dancing'?",
        "Answer": "Patrick Swayze and Jennifer Grey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Planet of the Apes', which planet does astronaut Charlton Heston actually find himself on?",
        "Answer": "Earth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Saving Private Ryan' is set around which war?",
        "Answer": "World War 2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Quentin Tarantino film won the main prize at the 1994 Cannes film festival?",
        "Answer": "'Pulp Fiction'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What sport was the subject of the 1996 film 'Happy Gilmore' starring Adam Sandler?",
        "Answer": "Golf"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor provided the voice for Captain John Smith in the 1995 film 'Pocohontas'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Gibson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Friends' what is Joey and Chandler's favourite TV show?",
        "Answer": "'Baywatch'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does Michael Douglas play a character who's car has a licence plate of 'D-FENS'?",
        "Answer": "'Falling Down'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What British TV show is the equivalent ot the American 'College Bowl'?",
        "Answer": "'University Challenge'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1986 John Landis film, how many 'Amigos' were there?",
        "Answer": "Three"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor has the real name of Maurice Micklewhite?",
        "Answer": "Michael Caine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Red Dwarf', what is the name of the ship's computer?",
        "Answer": "Holly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Created by Mike Judge, which cartoon characters first appeared on MTV in 1993?",
        "Answer": "Beavis and Butthead"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Tatum O'Neal when she received the Best Supporting Actress Oscar for the film 'Paper Moon'?",
        "Answer": "10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV series was Fallon kidnapped by a UFO?",
        "Answer": "'The Colby's'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Paddington Bear's favourite type of sandwiches?",
        "Answer": "Marmalade"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Anthony Perkins' character in the film 'Psycho'?",
        "Answer": "Norman Bates"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1997 comedy starred Elizabeth Hurley and Mike Myers?",
        "Answer": "'Austin Powers : Internation Man Of Mystery'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Wonder Woman in the TV series of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Lynda Carter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the surname of the family whose children were looked after by Mary Poppins?",
        "Answer": "Banks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was the BBC soap opera 'Eldorado' set?",
        "Answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which European country was actor Bruce Willis born?",
        "Answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first product to be advertised on British TV?",
        "Answer": "Toothpaste"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the thief Neil McCauley in the 1995 'Heat'?",
        "Answer": "Robert De Niro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the sheriff of Nottingham in the film 'Robin Hood: Prince Of Theives'?",
        "Answer": "Alan Rickman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the boxing film 'Rocky', what was Rocky's surname?",
        "Answer": "Balboa"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Frances Gumm is the real name of which actress?",
        "Answer": "Judy Garland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film shows the origin of Indiana Jones' fear of snakes?",
        "Answer": "Indiana Jones And The Last Crusade"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What religion are the Osmonds?",
        "Answer": "Mormon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the ficticious suburb where Coronation Street is set?",
        "Answer": "Weatherfield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Humphrey Bogart and Lauren Bacall first star together?",
        "Answer": "'To Have And Have Not'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played Barbella in the film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Jane Fonda"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1986 film 'Platoon'?",
        "Answer": "Oliver Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what film did Humphrey Bogart win his only Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'The African Queen'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Oscar winning actor died on June 27th, 2001?",
        "Answer": "Jack Lemmon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Film and TV star only spoke for the first time in 'The Karnival Kid', his ninth appearance on-screen?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Superman's hometown on Earth?",
        "Answer": "Smallville"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Around which war is the 1986 film 'Platoon' based?",
        "Answer": "Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Fred in the 1994 film 'The Flintstones'?",
        "Answer": "John Goodman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1958 film features the songs 'Some Enchanted Evening', 'There Is Nothing Like A Dame' and 'Happy Talk'?",
        "Answer": "'South Pacific'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer won a best actress Oscar playing the character of Loretta Castorini?",
        "Answer": "Cher"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed 'Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels'?",
        "Answer": "Guy Ritchie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Still showing today, what was the first ever programme to be televised on Channel 4?",
        "Answer": "'Countdown'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous acting couple have matching tatoos and wear locket's on their necks containing each others blood?",
        "Answer": "Angelina Jolie and Billy Bob Thornton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is the 1984 film 'The Killing Fields' set?",
        "Answer": "Cambodia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer has appeared in films playing characters called 'Danny Fisher', 'Glenn Tyler' and 'Lucky Jackson'?",
        "Answer": "Elvis Presley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme for the Bond film 'The Spy Who Loved Me'?",
        "Answer": "Carly Simon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors were nominated for best actor awards at the Oscars in 1991, both for playing wheelchair-bound characters?",
        "Answer": "Tom Cruise (for 'Born On The Fourth Of July') and Daniel Day-Lewis (for 'My Left Foot')."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the main villain in the cartoon 'Wacky Races'?",
        "Answer": "Dick Dastardly"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor received 4 million dollars for his 10 minutes on screen in the film 'Superman'?",
        "Answer": "Marlon Brando"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The Two Jakes' was a sequel to what 1974 film?",
        "Answer": "'Chinatown'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played James Bond in the film 'You Only Live Twice'?",
        "Answer": "Sean Connery"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film director was born Allen Stewart Konigsberg in 1935?",
        "Answer": "Woody Allen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1962 film is based on T. E. Lawrence's book 'The Seven Pillars Of Wisdom'?",
        "Answer": "'Lawrence Of Arabia'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Christopher Walken won the best supporting actor Oscar in 1979 for his role in which film?",
        "Answer": "The Deer Hunter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was actor Mel Gibson born?",
        "Answer": "America"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Alfred Hitchcock never won a best director Oscar, but which of his films won a best film Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'Rebecca'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first name of John Travolta's character in 'Grease'?",
        "Answer": "Danny"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the character of Lord Flasheart who appeared in several episodes of the TV comedy series 'Blackadder'?",
        "Answer": "Rik Mayall"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played in the title role in the 1972 film 'Junior Bonner'?",
        "Answer": "Steve McQueen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What unusual physical characteristic does the Bond villain Scaramanga have in the film 'The Man With The Golden Gun'?",
        "Answer": "A third nipple"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The three part TV series 'Killer' introduced which detective inspector to our screens in 1983?",
        "Answer": "Taggart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2001, which 3 Steven Spielberg films are among the top ten highest grossing films of all time?",
        "Answer": "'Jurassic Park', 'E.T.' and 'The Lost World'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Ross in friends?",
        "Answer": "David Schwimmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays 'Daffy' in the film 'The Beach'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Carlyle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following are the first names of a married couple who acted in the 2000 film 'Traffic'? Uma and Stephen, Catherine and Michael or Andie and Ethan?",
        "Answer": "Michael and Catherine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city did the action in the film 'The French Connection' take place?",
        "Answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1983 film starred Glenn Close, Jeff Goldblum, William Hurt and Kevin Kline?",
        "Answer": "'The Big Chill'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Name the Simpson's cat?",
        "Answer": "Snowball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How are Fizz, Milo, Jake and Bella better known collectively?",
        "Answer": "The Tweenies"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Jodie Foster play a character called 'Tallulah'?",
        "Answer": "'Bugsy Malone'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the TV show 'Bonanza' changed to?",
        "Answer": "'Ponderosa'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the TV series 'Worzel Gummidge'?",
        "Answer": "Jon Pertwee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Steve Buscemi's character in the Coen brothers film 'The Big Lebowski'? Donny, Smokey or Dude?",
        "Answer": "Donny"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How is Marie Lawrie better known in the music world?",
        "Answer": "Lulu"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian partnered Robert Powell in the TV comedy series 'The Detectives'?",
        "Answer": "Jasper Carrott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Linda Blair's character in the film 'The Exorcist'? Carrie, Regan or Tanni?",
        "Answer": "Regan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film starring David Bowie was based on the novel 'The Seed And The Sower'?",
        "Answer": "'Merry Christmas Mr. Lawrence'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sean Connery has won one Oscar for best actor -  in which film?",
        "Answer": "The Untouchables"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What film was advertised with the slogan 'an adventure 65 million years in the making'?",
        "Answer": "'Jurassic Park'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1978, who became the first cartoon character to have a star on the Hollywood Walk of Fame?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the only word spoken by mime artist Marcel Marceau in the 1976 film 'Silent Movie'?",
        "Answer": "'No'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actress Emma Thompson won an Oscar for which 1992 film?",
        "Answer": "Howard's End"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film did Jack Nicholson win the best actor Oscar in 1984?",
        "Answer": "Terms of Endearment"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the characted played by Ray Park in 'Star Wars Episode 1 : The Phantom Menace'?",
        "Answer": "Darth Maul"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film star has a statue in Leicester Square in London?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Miss Piggy from the Muppets' surname?",
        "Answer": "Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the 1998 sequel to the film 'Babe' called?",
        "Answer": "'Babe: Pig In The City'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "John List who murdered his family and then disappeared inspired which character in a 1995 film?",
        "Answer": "Keyser Soze (in 'The Usual Suspects')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Jim in the TV comedy series 'The Royle Family'?",
        "Answer": "Ricky Tomlinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is actress Jamie Lee Curtis' famous mother?",
        "Answer": "Janet Leigh"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the only actor to speak in Mel Brooks' film 'Silent Movie' saying the word 'No'?",
        "Answer": "Marcel Marceau"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Roxanne' starring Steve Martin is based on which classic French film?",
        "Answer": "'Cyrano De Bergerac'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Dougal in 'The Magic Roundabout'?",
        "Answer": "Dog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Richard Kimble in a 1993 film which was based on a sixties TV show?",
        "Answer": "Harrison Ford (in 'The Fugitive')."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the the 1993 film 'The Adventures Of Huck Finn'?",
        "Answer": "Elijah Wood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which real life gangster has been portrayed in films by Rod Steiger, Jason Robards and Robert De Niro?",
        "Answer": "Al Capone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of George Lucas' dog, which gave it's name to a famous film character?",
        "Answer": "Indiana Jones"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who created the TV series 'The Simpsons'?",
        "Answer": "Matt Groening"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the profession at the centre of the film 'Backdraft'?",
        "Answer": "Firefighting"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Bond villain had the first name 'Auric'?",
        "Answer": "Goldfinger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor has played the policeman Nick Rowan on TV?",
        "Answer": "Nick Berry (in 'Heartbeat')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What TV show connects Dan Castellaneta, Julie Kavnar and Yeardley Smith?",
        "Answer": "'The Simpsons'  (they provide some of the character's voices)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film villain had David Prowse play it's body, Sebastian Shaw play it's face, and James Earl Jones provide it's voice?",
        "Answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor links 'Legends Of The Fall', 'Interview With The Vampire' and 'Ocean's Eleven'?",
        "Answer": "Brad Pitt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Benny The Ball', 'Choo-Choo', 'Fancy Fancy' and 'Spook' were part of which cartoon characters gang?",
        "Answer": "Topcat's"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film by Don Siegel is about aliens stealing the mind and bodies of human beings?",
        "Answer": "'Invasion Of The Body Snatchers'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon dog is sometimes referred to as 'the biggest clown in town'?",
        "Answer": "Huckleberry Hound"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Around which war is the film 'The Guns Of Navarone' set?",
        "Answer": "World War II"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which tough-guy actor sang 'I Talk to the Trees' in the 1970 film 'Paint Your Wagon'?",
        "Answer": "Clint Eastwood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1985 film was directed by Robert Zemeckis and featured the characted Marty McFly?",
        "Answer": "Back To The Future"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1968 film features the characters Caractacus Potts and Truly Scrumptious?",
        "Answer": "'Chitty Chitty Bang Bang'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "During the 1990s which three people hosted the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "Billy Crystal, Whoopi Goldberg and David Letterman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV game show 'The Crystal Maze', what was the name of the original zone which was later replaced by 'Ocean World'?",
        "Answer": "The Industrial Zone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which series of action films does the character of John McClane appear?",
        "Answer": "'Die Hard'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film did Audrey Hepburn win her only Oscar?",
        "Answer": "'Roman Holiday'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the sequel to the 1991 film the 'Addams Family' called?",
        "Answer": "Addams Family Values"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Better known as a comedian, who sang the theme tune for the TV series 'One Foot In The Grave'?",
        "Answer": "Eric Idle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'Blue Peter', who was the first presenter to actually be called Peter?",
        "Answer": "Peter Purves"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1977 film was introduced by the words, 'A long time ago in a galaxy far away...'?",
        "Answer": "'Star Wars'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1992 film does the character Catherine Tramell appear?",
        "Answer": "Basic Instinct"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was advertised with the line 'In space, no-one can hear you scream'?",
        "Answer": "Alien"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor is the lead singer with the rock group 30 odd foot of grunts?",
        "Answer": "Russell Crowe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was actor David Niven's final film?",
        "Answer": "'Curse Of The Pink Panther'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous duo began in a 1940 MGM short called 'Puss Gets the Boot'?",
        "Answer": "Tom and Jerry"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Speed' what is the speed that the bus must not go below?",
        "Answer": "50 miles per hour"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which decade was the TV series 'Grange Hill' first broadcast - the 1970s or the 1980s?",
        "Answer": "1970s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who sang the theme tune to the TV series 'Minder'?",
        "Answer": "Denis Waterman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was Arnold Swarzenegger born?",
        "Answer": "Austria"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1974 film 'Blazing Saddles'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Brooks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Dennis Potter's TV series 'The Singing Detective', what was the name Michael Gambon's character which was also the name of famous fictional detective?",
        "Answer": "Philip Marlowe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film character do the japanese call 'Mr. Kissy Kissy Bang Bang'?",
        "Answer": "James Bond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1976 gangster film are the gangsters played by children?",
        "Answer": "'Bugsy Malone'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1977 film did John Travolta get his first starring role?",
        "Answer": "'Saturday Night Fever'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Curse Of The Pink Panther', which actor plays Inspector Clouseau after having plastic surgery?",
        "Answer": "Roger Moore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Scaramanga in the James Bond film 'The man with the golden gun'?",
        "Answer": "Christopher Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which English city was named Aquae Sulis by the Romans?",
        "Answer": "Bath"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1982 British film is thought to have had 300,000 extras appear in it?",
        "Answer": "'Gandhi'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is America's equivalent of 'University Challenge' called?",
        "Answer": "'College Bowl'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1993 film does the character Dr Richard Kimble appear?",
        "Answer": "The Fugitive"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the 1965 film 'The Cincinnati Kid'?",
        "Answer": "Steve McQueen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1998 film 'The Big Lebowski', what is the dude's favourite cocktail?",
        "Answer": "White Russian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1995 animated Disney film featured a raccoon called Meeko and a hummingbird called Flit?",
        "Answer": "'Pocahontas'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 19973 film starred Ron Howard, Harrison Ford and Richard Dreyfuss?",
        "Answer": "'American Graffiti'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played Dorien in the TV sitcom 'Birds of a Feather'?",
        "Answer": "Lesley Joseph"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of creature is Indiana Jones scared of? Snakes, Spiders or Rats?",
        "Answer": "Snakes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Fred Flintstone's wife called?",
        "Answer": "Wilma"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Toy Story 2' what is the name of Buzz Lightyear's arch enemy?",
        "Answer": "Emperor Zurg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what name is the comic book character of Oswald Cobblepot better known?",
        "Answer": "The Penguin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played 'The Elephant Man' in a David Lynch film?",
        "Answer": "John Hurt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy series 'The Good Life', what was the surname of the Good's neighbours?",
        "Answer": "Leadbetter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1963 film had a budget of 44 million dollars which if adjusted for inflation would make it one of the most expensive films ever made?",
        "Answer": "'Cleopatra'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Almost Famous' based on his own experiences as a rock reporter in the 70s for Led Zeppelin?",
        "Answer": "Cameron Crowe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mickey Mouse have eyes which have pupils for the first time in which 1940 film?",
        "Answer": "'Fantasia'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character lives at 1313 Webfoot Walk?",
        "Answer": "Donald Duck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress was born Margaret Mary Emily Anne Hyra?",
        "Answer": "Meg Ryan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV detective kept his gun in a biscuit jar?",
        "Answer": "Jim Rockford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film featured Robin Williams playing an English teacher called John Keating?",
        "Answer": "'Dead Poets Society'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2003, which of the following has been the most profitable movie series: James Bond, Indiana Jones or Star Wars?",
        "Answer": "James Bond"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which type of animal was Robin Hood in the Disney cartoon film 'Robin Hood'?",
        "Answer": "A fox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1999 film featured a sequence in which 7,900 rubber frogs were used?",
        "Answer": "Magnolia"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film released in the year 2000, was advertised with the slogan 'Escape or Die Frying'?",
        "Answer": "'Chicken Run'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what was the name of the first cartoon Scratchy appeared in? 'The Happy Cat', 'Scratchy Goes West' or 'Steamboat Scratchy'?",
        "Answer": "The Happy Cat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Charlie's surname in 'Charlie and the Chocolate Factory'?",
        "Answer": "Bucket"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were Dirty Den's first two words on his 'Eastenders' comeback in 2003?",
        "Answer": "Hello princess"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which James Bond film does the character of Solitaire appear?",
        "Answer": "'Live and Let Die'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress plays the character of Tracy who marries James Bond in 'On her majesty's secret service'?",
        "Answer": "Diana Rigg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who hosted the TV show 'The Krypton Factor'?",
        "Answer": "Gordon Burns"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the 10 pin bowling player played by John Turturro in 'The Big Lebowski'? Satan, Lucifer or Jesus?",
        "Answer": "Jesus"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the subject of the Mel Brooks film subtitled 'Men in Tights'?",
        "Answer": "Robin Hood"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "John Huston directed a 1975 film called 'The Man Who Would Be ____' what?",
        "Answer": "King"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Clint Eastwood first appear as the 'Man with no name'?",
        "Answer": "'A Fistful Of Dollars'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The song 'You've got to pick a pocket or two' featured in what 1968 film?",
        "Answer": "'Oliver!'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At what age did Marilyn Monroe die?",
        "Answer": "36"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the cow in the childrens TV show 'The Magic Roundabout'?",
        "Answer": "Ermintrude"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Robert Wagner's wife in the TV series 'Hart to Hart'?",
        "Answer": "Stephanie Powers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series had characters called Jack Rolfe, Ken Masters and Claude Du Pont?",
        "Answer": "'Howard's Way'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state is the 1953 film 'From Here To Eternity' set?",
        "Answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress provided the voices for Jane and Brooke Shields in the 1999 films 'Tarzan' and 'South Park: Bigger, Longer and Uncut'?",
        "Answer": "Minnie Driver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what 1991 film did Robert De Niro pay a dentist $5,000 to make his teeth look bad, and then after filming paid $20,000 to get them fixed?",
        "Answer": "'Cape Fear'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what type of animal is Santa's Little Helper?",
        "Answer": "Dog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which female singer performed the first song on Top Of The Pops?",
        "Answer": "Dusty Springfield"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first name of Wayne's friend in 'Wayne's World'?",
        "Answer": "Garth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state is the 2002 film 'Insomnia', starring Al Pacino set?",
        "Answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you first have come across a sorcerer called Yesnid?",
        "Answer": "'Fantasia'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1999 film was the last to be directed by Stanley Kubrick?",
        "Answer": "'Eyes Wide Shut'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Island Of Lost Dreams' was part of the title to which 2002 movie sequel?",
        "Answer": "Spy Kids 2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what country was actress Greta Garbo born?",
        "Answer": "Sweden"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actresses shared the best actress Oscar in 1968?",
        "Answer": "Barbra Striesand and Katherine Hepburn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On the set of what film did Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman fall in love and then got married later in the same year?",
        "Answer": "'Days Of Thunder'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film 'Ben-Hur' was nominated for 12 awards at the 1960 Oscars. How many did it win?",
        "Answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of Snow White's seven dwarfs would come first alphabetically?",
        "Answer": "Bashful."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What now-common four-letter word was first heard on the screen in the film 'Gone With The Wind'?",
        "Answer": "'Damn'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The film '10 things I hate about you' is based on which Shakespeare play?",
        "Answer": "'The Taming Of The Shrew'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what role is actor Buster Crabbe best known?",
        "Answer": "Flash Gordon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the Rocky films was released in 1983?",
        "Answer": "Rocky III"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Thunderbirds', what was the registration number of Lady Penelope's Rolls Royce?",
        "Answer": "'FAB 1'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Wizard Of Oz', what was the Scarecrow looking for?",
        "Answer": "A brain"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the line in 'Casablanca' which is often misquoted as 'Play it again, Sam', what song is Sam asked to play?",
        "Answer": "As Time Goes By"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which film and television role is actor Leonard Nimoy best known?",
        "Answer": "Spock (in 'Star Trek')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How did Matt Groening, creator of the Simpsons, come up with the names Homer and Bart?",
        "Answer": "Homer was the name of his father, Bart was an anagram of Brat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who provided the voice for Woody in Toy Story?",
        "Answer": "Tom Hanks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Roy Rogers' horse called?",
        "Answer": "Trigger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1982 film featured the line ''More human than human' is our motto.'?",
        "Answer": "'Blade Runner'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animal was Baloo in Walt Disney's 'The Jungle Book'?",
        "Answer": "A bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Cujo' what type of dog was 'Cujo'?",
        "Answer": "A St Bernard"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'Trumpton', what was the profession of Hugh, Pugh, Barney McGrew, Cuthbert, Dibble and Grub?",
        "Answer": "Firemen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2001, who is the only film director to have won 4 Best Director awards at the Oscars?",
        "Answer": "John Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "With which 1980s TV show would you associate the character Terry McCann?",
        "Answer": "'Minder'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following films wasn't directed by David Lynch? The Straight Story, Existenz or Dune?",
        "Answer": "Existenz"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Star Trek', from which planet did Spock's mother come?",
        "Answer": "Earth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who had a UK top ten hit in July, 1980 with '9 to 5'?",
        "Answer": "Sheena Easton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed, produced and starred in the 1977 film 'High Anxiety'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Brooks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film director directed the 1956 film 'The Killing'?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred with Jack Lemmon in 'The Odd Couple'?",
        "Answer": "Walter Matthau"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Shakespearian character did Leonardo DiCaprio play in a 1996 film directed by Baz Luhrmann?",
        "Answer": "Romeo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor was Madonna married to between 1985 and 1989?",
        "Answer": "Sean Penn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Sesame Street' character is named after a taxi driver in 'It's A Wonderful Life'?",
        "Answer": "Ernie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which pair of twin puppet pigs first appeared on UK television in 1957?",
        "Answer": "Pinky and Perky"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which make of car was James Dean driving when he was killed in 1955?",
        "Answer": "Porsche"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Butch Cassidy in the 1969 film 'Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Newman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the sequel to the 1987 film 'Three Men and a Baby' called?",
        "Answer": "'Three Men And A Little Lady'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who co-wrote 'Fawlty Towers' with John Cleese?",
        "Answer": "Connie Booth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which star of many comedy films died during the making of the 1994 film 'Wagon's East'?",
        "Answer": "John Candy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which A. S. played Manuel in the TV show 'Fawlty Towers'?",
        "Answer": "Andrew Sachs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'The Simpsons', what relation is Herb Powell to Homer Simpson?",
        "Answer": "Brother"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Rambo's first name?",
        "Answer": "John"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What make of car does TV's Mr Bean drive?",
        "Answer": "Mini"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Star Wars', what do the letters 'TIE' stand for in 'TIE Fighter'?",
        "Answer": "Twin Ion Engine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Better known as an actor, who directed the film 'A Bronx Tale'?",
        "Answer": "Robert De Niro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film Goldeneye, which British actor played agent 006?",
        "Answer": "Sean Bean"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first in Krzysztof Kieslowski's 'Three Colours' trilogy of films called? Red, White or Blue?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which film did the pop group Heaven 17 take their name?",
        "Answer": "'A Clockwork Orange'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Dirty Harry' what was Harry's surname?",
        "Answer": "Callahan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the modern film version of 'Cyrano de Bergerac' starring Steve Martin?",
        "Answer": "'Roxanne'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1963 film won 3 Oscar nominations for Best Supporting Actress?",
        "Answer": "'Tom Jones'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress was only 10 years old when she won a best supporting actress Oscar for the film 'Paper Moon'?",
        "Answer": "Tatum O'Neal"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Tinkerbell in Steven Spielberg's film 'Hook'?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city did James Bond get married?",
        "Answer": "Munich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed, produced and starred in the film 'The Mirror Has Two Faces'?",
        "Answer": "Barbra Streisand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At the Academy Awards in 1999, 'The Truman Show' was nominated in which of the following categories? Best Actor, Best Supporting Actor or Best Supporting Actress?",
        "Answer": "Best Supporting Actor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Orson Welles when he made 'Citizen Kane'? 26, 36 or 46?",
        "Answer": "26"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Buffy The Vampire Slayer', what is Buffy's last name?",
        "Answer": "Summers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1985 film did Harrison Ford play detective John Book?",
        "Answer": "Witness"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What film won the best picture, best director and best actor Oscars in 1995?",
        "Answer": "Forrest Gump"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does VHS stand for as used in video tapes and recorders?",
        "Answer": "Video Home System"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Cher's first solo number one hit in the UK?",
        "Answer": "'The Shoop Shoop Song (It's In His Kiss)'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film director's real name was Terrence Nezman?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the last actress to win an Oscar for Best Actress for playing the title character of the film?",
        "Answer": "Jessica Tandy (for 'Driving Miss Daisy')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what film did Tommy Lee Jones win the best supporting actor Oscar in 1994?",
        "Answer": "The Fugitive"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Requiring 800,000 hours to generate all the images, what 1995 film was the first fully computer generated full length feature film?",
        "Answer": "'Toy Story'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor starred as Dr Doolittle in the 1967 film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Rex Harrison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the mouse that Dumbo the elephant made friends with in the Disney cartoon?",
        "Answer": "Timothy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy series 'Steptoe and Son', what was the name of Steptoe's horse?",
        "Answer": "Hercules"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV medical drama was set in Oxbridge General Hospital and was originally entitled 'Calling Nurse Roberts'?",
        "Answer": "'Emergency Ward 10'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which group sang the theme tune to the TV series 'Brush Strokes'?",
        "Answer": "Dexy's Midnight Runners"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1969 film features the song 'Raindrops Keep Falling On My Head'?",
        "Answer": "'Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Postman Pat's cat called?",
        "Answer": "Jess"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On what childrens TV show would you find Spud the Scarecrow?",
        "Answer": "Bob The Builder"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many of the seven dwarfs had beards?",
        "Answer": "6 (Dopey was the only one not to have one)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were Jake and Elwood better known as in a 1980 film?",
        "Answer": "The Blues Brothers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Jan Sterling in 1956 and Suzanna Hamilton in 1984 both played the part of Julia in two different versions of what film?",
        "Answer": "1984"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Bonnie and Clyde in the 1967 film?",
        "Answer": "Warren Beaty and Faye Dunaway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Inspector Morse on TV?",
        "Answer": "John Thaw"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who, in 1996, became the first actress to be paid 10 million dollars for a role in a film and what was the film?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts in 'Mary Reilly'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "William Pratt is the real name of which actor, best known for his work in horror films?",
        "Answer": "Boris Karloff"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Cameron Diaz and Julia Roberts appear as love rivals in which 90ÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s romantic comedy?",
        "Answer": "'My Best Friends Wedding'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the female judge on the first of ITV's 'Pop Idol' series?",
        "Answer": "Nicki Chapman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1974 film features a character called Leatherface, who was based on real-life mass murderer Ed Gein?",
        "Answer": "'The Texas Chainsaw Massacre'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American city is the film 'Minority Report' set?",
        "Answer": "Washington D.C."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1984 film does 'Gizmo' appear?",
        "Answer": "'Gremlins'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the leading role in the film 'The Man Who Wasn't There'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Bob Thornton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV puppet has its own museum in Shipley in Yorkshire?",
        "Answer": "Sooty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the children's TV show 'Tiswas', what did the letters in the title stand for?",
        "Answer": "Today Is Saturday Watch & Smile"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Jim Morrison in the film 'The Doors'?",
        "Answer": "Val Kilmer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was actress Vivien Leigh born?",
        "Answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Big Brother' was the title of the first episode of which long running TV comedy series?",
        "Answer": "'Only Fools And Horses'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred in the films 'Scarface', 'One Fine Day' and 'Batman Returns'?",
        "Answer": "Michelle Pfeiffer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film did Oprah Winfrey make her big screen acting debut?",
        "Answer": "'The Color Purple'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1974 sequel won the best picture award at the 1975 Oscars?",
        "Answer": "The Godfather, Part II"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which weekly BBC TV show was axed in January 2003 after nearly 40 years?",
        "Answer": "'Tomorrow's World'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what decade did the BBC begin television broadcasting?",
        "Answer": "1930s"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character sometimes had trouble controlling Musky and Vince?",
        "Answer": "Deputy Dawg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Jack Nicholson play the character of Randle Patrick McMurphy?",
        "Answer": "'One flew over the cuckoo's nest'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film has been nominated for the most Oscars in one year?",
        "Answer": "All About Eve (at the 1951 ceremony)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The line 'Get busy living, or get busy dying' is spoken by the actor Morgan Freeman in which film?",
        "Answer": "'The Shawshank Redemption'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city is the soap opera 'Brookside' set?",
        "Answer": "Liverpool"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Batman in the 1989 film called 'Batman'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Keaton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Bond film featured a theme tune sung by Tom Jones?",
        "Answer": "Thunderball"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'Sex and the City' star is actor Matthew Broderick married to?",
        "Answer": "Sarah Jessica Parker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character from the Popeye cartoon liked eating hamburgers?",
        "Answer": "Wimpy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was the recent 'Lord Of The Rings' movie filmed?",
        "Answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which century was the 1995 film 'Judge Dredd' set?",
        "Answer": "22nd"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous American family live at 742 Evergreen Terrace?",
        "Answer": "'The Simpsons'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following didn't appear in the film 'Stand By Me'? Corey Haim, River Phoenix or Keifer Sutherland?",
        "Answer": "Corey Haim"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the spiv played by James Beck in DadÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s Army?",
        "Answer": "Private Walker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first Bond film to be based on one of Ian Fleming's short stories and not on one of his novels?",
        "Answer": "'For Your Eyes Only'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Jean De Florette', what is Gerard Depardieu's character looking for? Water, his twin brother, or the Holy Grail?",
        "Answer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won a Golden Globe best actor award in 1999 for his performance in 'The Truman Show'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Carrey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1980 film 'The Elephant Man'?",
        "Answer": "David Lynch"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor famously said the line 'Here's looking at you, kid' in the film 'Casablanca'?",
        "Answer": "Humphrey Bogart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which rock band was the subject of a 1991 Oliver Stone film?",
        "Answer": "The Doors"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous TV and film actress got engaged to musician Kid Rock in April 2002?",
        "Answer": "Pamela Anderson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV comedy series 'Red Dwarf', what letter does Rimmer have on his forehead?",
        "Answer": "'H'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Frank and Betty's daughter in the TV comedy series 'Some Mother's Do Have Em'?",
        "Answer": "Jessica"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Mr Orange in 'Reservoir Dogs'?",
        "Answer": "Tim Roth"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first film that Alfred Hitchcock made in Hollywood and the only one that won a Best Picture Oscar?",
        "Answer": "Rebecca"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which British city is the 1997 film 'Twin Town' set?",
        "Answer": "Swansea"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did actress Hayley Mills first appear?",
        "Answer": "'Tiger Bay'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the python in The Jungle book?",
        "Answer": "Kaa"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character in the TV show 'Sesame Street' lives in a trash can?",
        "Answer": "Oscar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of these was a 1948 Western starring John Wayne and directed by Howard Hawks? Red River, Yellow River or Moon River?",
        "Answer": "Red River"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Eliot Ness in the 1987 film 'The Untouchables'?",
        "Answer": "Kevin Costner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the line in 'Casablanca' which is often misquoted as 'Play it again, Sam'. What song is Sam asked to play?",
        "Answer": "'As Time Goes By'."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played a bisexual bank robber in the 1975 film 'Dog Day Afternoon'?",
        "Answer": "Al Pacino"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first female newsreader on 'News at 10'?",
        "Answer": "Anna Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film ends with the words 'It's the stuff that dreams are made of'?",
        "Answer": "The Maltese Falcon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American state was the film 'The Blair Witch Project' set?",
        "Answer": "Maryland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won an acting Oscar in 1999 for their performance in a film, which they appeared on screen for only 8 minutes?",
        "Answer": "Judi Dench"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1955 film does Frank Sinatra play Nathan Detroit?",
        "Answer": "'Guys and Dolls'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1946 film features the characters George Bailey and Clarence?",
        "Answer": "'It's a wonderful life'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Joey Boswell in Bread and later went on to direct the film 'Sliding Doors'?",
        "Answer": "Peter Howitt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Jimmy 'Popeye' Doyle in 'The French Connection'?",
        "Answer": "Gene Hackman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the main street in the TV soap opera 'Neighbours'?",
        "Answer": "Ramsay Street"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Rob Sering hosted the 'Night Gallery', but was more famous for hosting which other sci-fi series?",
        "Answer": "'The Twilight Zone'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of animals are the cartoon characters Chip and Dale?",
        "Answer": "Chipmunks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor had the real name of Bernard Schwartz?",
        "Answer": "Tony Curtis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV series featured a space-ship called 'Jupiter 11'?",
        "Answer": "'Lost In Space'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is Amelia Fieldmouse's famous cartoon brother?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress said 'I always did like a man in uniform. And that one fits you grand. Why don't you come up sometime and see me?'",
        "Answer": "Mae West"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of Bart Simpson's dog?",
        "Answer": "Santa's Little Helper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1991 film 'Cape Fear'?",
        "Answer": "Martin Scorcese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "An unproduced play 'Everybody Comes to Rick's' was made into which famous film?",
        "Answer": "'Casablanca'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first name of the cabin boy in 'Captain Pugwash'?",
        "Answer": "Tom"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1994 film featured Arnold Swarzenegger playing a pregnant man?",
        "Answer": "'Junior'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did a 'Starling' capture a 'Buffalo'?",
        "Answer": "Silence Of The Lambs"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 1985 film 'The Color Purple' won no Oscars, but how many nominations did it receive?",
        "Answer": "11"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Lord Of The Rings: The Two Towers' which character did Andy Serkis provide the voice for?",
        "Answer": "Gollum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1993 film does Kevin Kline play a look-alike hired to impersonate the President?",
        "Answer": "'Dave'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1967 film had the tagline 'Train them! Excite them! Arm them!...Then turn them loose on the Nazis!'?",
        "Answer": "'The Dirty Dozen'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1986 film had the tag-line 'Be afraid. Be very afraid.'?",
        "Answer": "'The Fly'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the leading role in the 1971 version of the film 'Get Carter' and who played him the 2000 version?",
        "Answer": "Michael Caine and Sylvester Stallone."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the four original presenters of the TV series 'Game For A Laugh'?",
        "Answer": "Jeremy Beadle, Henry Kelly, Matthew Kelly and Sarah Kennedy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Janet in the 1975 film 'The Rocky Horror Picture Show'?",
        "Answer": "Susan Sarandon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the Manager played by Ricky Jervais in the comedy series 'The Office'?",
        "Answer": "David Brent"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year was Steven Spielberg born? 1936, 1946 or 1956?",
        "Answer": "1946"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the surname of the professor played by Rex Harrisson in the 1964 film 'My Fair Lady'?",
        "Answer": "Higgins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "When Walt Disney's seven dwarfs went off to work in the mines, what were they mining?",
        "Answer": "Diamonds"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the city where the Wizard of Oz lived?",
        "Answer": "The Emerald City"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Barbara Striesand's first film?",
        "Answer": "'Funny Girl'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What American TV show had a spin-off called 'Joanie and Chachi'?",
        "Answer": "'Happy Days'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did Marilyn Monroe famously sing 'Happy Birthday Mr President' to John F. Kennedy?",
        "Answer": "1962"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the children's TV show 'The Magic Roundabout', what was the name of the cow?",
        "Answer": "Ermintrude"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Sabrina in the television show 'Sabrina the Teenage Witch'?",
        "Answer": "Melissa Joan Hart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the leading role in the 1986 film 'The Golden Child'?",
        "Answer": "Eddie Murphy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The TV comedy series 'George And Mildred' was a spin-off from which other sitcom?",
        "Answer": "'Man About The House'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who became the youngest person to be crowned Mr Universe in 1967 and later became a famous Hollywood actor?",
        "Answer": "Arnold Swarzenegger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which US state is home to cartoon character Deputy Dawg?",
        "Answer": "Mississippi"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor suffered a fatal heart attack during the filming of 'Gladiator'?",
        "Answer": "Oliver Reed."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American actor died at the age of 22 after collapsing outside a club in 1993?",
        "Answer": "River Phoenix"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress from the TV show 'Friends' began her acting career advertising Tampax?",
        "Answer": "Courtney Cox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won the best actor award for the film 'Ben Hur'?",
        "Answer": "Charlton Heston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1983 film starred David Bowie, Susan Sarandon and Catherine Deneuve?",
        "Answer": "'The Hunger'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How much is the gold bullion worth in 'The Italian Job'?",
        "Answer": "$4,000,000"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor provides the voice for Rocky in the film 'Chicken Run'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Gibson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 'Thunderbirds', what colour was Lady Penelope's Rolls Royce?",
        "Answer": "Pink"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two characters in 'Friends' got married in Las Vegas?",
        "Answer": "Ross and Rachel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1992 film starring Kristy Swanson is also the name of a TV series?",
        "Answer": "'Buffy The Vampire Slayer'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was James Dean's last film?",
        "Answer": "'Giant'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character was kidnapped by a UFO in 'The Colbys'?",
        "Answer": "Fallon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Peter Pan in Steven Spielberg's film 'Hook'?",
        "Answer": "Robin Williams"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Truman Show' what was the first name of the character played by Jim Carrey?",
        "Answer": "Truman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Alec Baldwin play the character of Jack Ryan?",
        "Answer": "'The Hunt For Red October'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the full title to the sequel to the film 'Home Alone'?",
        "Answer": "'Home Alone 2: Lost In New York'."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the year 2000, who were the only two members of the original cast of 'Eastenders' still in the show?",
        "Answer": "Wendy Richard and Adam Woodyatt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the studio executive Griffin Mill in the 1992 film 'The Player'?",
        "Answer": "Tim Robbins"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 2001 film 'Black Hawk Down'?",
        "Answer": "Ridley Scott"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Indiana Jones looking for in the film 'Indiana Jones And The Last Crusade'?",
        "Answer": "The Holy Grail"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What are the four different colours of Blue Peter badges?",
        "Answer": "Blue, Green, Silver and Gold"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Peter Mayhew is best known for playing what Star Wars character?",
        "Answer": "Chewbacca"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first 'Carry On' film called?",
        "Answer": "'Carry On Sergeant'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'I'm Alan Partridge', in which English town does Alan broadcast his radio show?",
        "Answer": "Norwich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who hosted the TV quiz show 'Ask The Family'?",
        "Answer": "Robert Robinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Nora Batty in the TV series 'Last Of The Summer Wine'?",
        "Answer": "Kathy Staff"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Casey Kasem provided the voice of which character in Scooby Doo?",
        "Answer": "Shaggy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which London football club was the first in England to install an artificial pitch?",
        "Answer": "Queens Park Rangers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous cartoon character first appeared on-screen in the 1934 cartoon 'The Wise Little Hen'?",
        "Answer": "Donald Duck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character has an anchor tatooed on his arm?",
        "Answer": "Popeye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year did Channel 4 begin broadcasting?",
        "Answer": "1982"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Monty Python's Flying Circus, what type of animal was Dinsdale?",
        "Answer": "A giant hedgehog"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1987 film stars Eddie Murphy as Axel Foley?",
        "Answer": "Beverly Hills Cop II"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character has three nephews called Huey, Dewey and Louis?",
        "Answer": "Donald Duck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred in 'Wild Things' and the 'Scream' trilogy?",
        "Answer": "Neve Campbell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1993 film 'The Fugitive'? Peter Weir, Andrew Davis or Wolfgang Peterson?",
        "Answer": "Andrew Davis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Father Peter in the TV series 'Ballykissangel'?",
        "Answer": "Stephen Tompkinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which Saturday morning TV show might you have seen the Phantom Flan Flinger?",
        "Answer": "Tiswas"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which American city was the TV show 'Cheers' set?",
        "Answer": "Boston"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the boat in the TV show 'The Love Boat'?",
        "Answer": "The Pacific Princess"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1980 horror film which spawned a number of sequels was directed by Sean S Cunningham?",
        "Answer": "'Friday The 13th'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at January 2000, what are the only two James Bond films where the title is not mentioned in the theme song?",
        "Answer": "'Dr No' and 'Octopussy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2001, who is the only actor to have won a best actor Oscar for his feature film debut, and what was the film?",
        "Answer": "Ben Kingsley, 'Ghandi'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the female lead in the 1933 film 'King Kong'?",
        "Answer": "Fay Wray"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character that O J Simpson played in the 'Naked Gun' films?",
        "Answer": "Officer Nordberg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV detective had a dog called simply 'Dog'?",
        "Answer": "Columbo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the childrens TV series, what was the name of the girl who looked after Bagpuss?",
        "Answer": "Emily"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1978 who became the youngest man to win a Best Actor Oscar for his performance in 'The Goodbye Girl'?",
        "Answer": "Richard Dreyfuss"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of John Wayne's final film?",
        "Answer": "'The Shootist'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Where did the Clangers live?",
        "Answer": "On the moon"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which movie actor has played characters including Jack Ryan and Dr Richard Kimble?",
        "Answer": "Harrisson Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1981, who took over from Tom Baker in the TV series 'Doctor Who'?",
        "Answer": "Peter Davison"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won a Golden Globe for playing the character Satine in the 2001 film 'Moulin Rouge'?",
        "Answer": "Nicole Kidman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous cartoon bird appeared for the first time in 1937 on the Porky Pig show?",
        "Answer": "Daffy Duck"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV detective has a sidekick called Seargent Lewis?",
        "Answer": "Inspector Morse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the films 'The Usual Suspects' and 'X-Men'?",
        "Answer": "Bryan Singer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Marilyn Monroe's full real name?",
        "Answer": "Norma-Jean Baker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1956 musical was based on the 1940 film 'The Philadelphia Story'?",
        "Answer": "'High Society'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2001, what are the only two films to receive 14 Oscar nominations?",
        "Answer": "'All About Eve' and 'Titanic'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1980 film did Jack Nicholson ad-lib the line 'Here's Johnny'?",
        "Answer": "'The Shining'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1992 film was advertised with the slogan 'Never let her out of your sight. Never let your guard down. Never fall in love.'?",
        "Answer": "'The Bodyguard'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What characted does Jack Nicholson play in the 1989 film 'Batman'? The Joker, The Penguin or The Riddler?",
        "Answer": "The Joker"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1984 film 'The Killing Fields'? Norman Jewison, Roland Joffe or Oliver Stone?",
        "Answer": "Roland Joffe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who's life inspired the 1987 film 'Personal Services'?",
        "Answer": "Cynthia Payne"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following appeared in both the films 'Magnolia' and 'Boogie Nights'? Mark Wahlberg, Julianne Moore or Tom Cruise?",
        "Answer": "Julianne Moore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the four Teenage Mutant Hero Turtles would come first alphabetically?",
        "Answer": "Donatello"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Death Wish'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Winner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at the year 2000, which three actors or actress won Oscars for roles primarily in a language other than English?",
        "Answer": "Sophia Loren, Robert De Niro and Roberto Benigni."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What job did Helen Hunt's character do in the film 'As Good As It Gets'?",
        "Answer": "Waitress"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Jim Phelps in the 1996 film 'Mission: Impossible'?",
        "Answer": "Jon Voigt"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor more famous for his roles in horror films played Sherlock Holmes in a 1968 TV series?",
        "Answer": "Peter Cushing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1956, who became the first actor to be nominated for an Oscar posthumously?",
        "Answer": "James Dean"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV character did Matt Frewer invent from an idea he had from a road sign?",
        "Answer": "Max Headroom"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors played the two character who traded places in the 1983 comedy 'Trading Places'?",
        "Answer": "Dan Aykroyd and Eddie Murphy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following actresses appeared in the film 'Top Gun'? Meg Ryan, Michelle Pfeiffer or Helen Hunt?",
        "Answer": "Meg Ryan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what film does Clint Eastwood play a radio d.j. stalked by an ex-fan?",
        "Answer": "'Play Misty For Me'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who won back-to-back best actor Oscars in the late 1930s?",
        "Answer": "Spencer Tracy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On TV, how was the character of Diana Prince better known?",
        "Answer": "Wonder Woman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two James Bond films did the character of 'Jaws' appear in?",
        "Answer": "'Moonraker' and 'The Spy Who Loved Me'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which television program ended with the line 'Time for bed said Zebedee'?",
        "Answer": "'The Magic Roundabout'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film about dancing featured the characters Frances 'Baby' Houseman and Johnny Castle?",
        "Answer": "'Dirty Dancing'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Lois Maxwell played which character in a number of James Bond films?",
        "Answer": "Miss Moneypenny"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the highest earning actress in America for the year 2000?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country is the soap opera 'The High Road' set?",
        "Answer": "Scotland"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Patrick Bateman in the film 'American Psycho'?",
        "Answer": "Christian Bale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What obstacle hindered the course of true love for Juliet Stevenson and Alan Rickman in the 1991 film 'Truly, Madly, Deeply'?",
        "Answer": "She was alive, he was dead."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which children's television show featured the characters of George, Zippy and Bungle?",
        "Answer": "'Rainbow'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the famous Monty Python sketch, what type of dead parrot did John Cleese take back to the shop?",
        "Answer": "Norwegian Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the possessed child in the film 'The Exorcist'?",
        "Answer": "Linda Blair"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which member of the 'A Team' was a pilot?",
        "Answer": "Murdoch"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Scooby Doo's favourite food?",
        "Answer": "Scooby Snacks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Frankenstein's monster in the 1931 film 'Frankenstein'?",
        "Answer": "Boris Karloff"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Bullitt's first name in the 1968 film 'Bullitt'?",
        "Answer": "Frank"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British band's first album was called 'Word Gets Around'?",
        "Answer": "The Stereophonics"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors played the main roles in the film 'Midnight Cowboy'?",
        "Answer": "Dustin Hoffman and Jon Voight"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who are Morty and Ferdie Fieldmouse's famous uncle?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many people does the Terminator played by Arnold Schwarzenegger kill in the film 'Terminator 2'? 0, 1 or 71?",
        "Answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film actor once played the detective David Addison on television?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not star in the 1976 film 'Network'? Faye Dunaway, Robert Duvall or Glenn Close?",
        "Answer": "Glenn Close"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which television show did Sherilyn Fenn play the character of Audrey Horne?",
        "Answer": "'Twin Peaks'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What film's three main characters are Brody, Hooper and Quint?",
        "Answer": "'Jaws'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played Alex in the TV show 'Family Ties'?",
        "Answer": "Michael J Fox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the killer in the film 'Halloween'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Myers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'The Unknown Stuntman' was the theme song for which TV action series?",
        "Answer": "'The Fall Guy'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What school did cartoon characters Pebbles and Bam Bam go to?",
        "Answer": "Bedrock High"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "As at Janurary 2000, which fictional character has been used in most films?",
        "Answer": "Sherlock Holmes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Robert Altman's 1992 film about Hollywood?",
        "Answer": "The Player"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress co-produced and starred in the 1999 film 'Never Been Kissed'?",
        "Answer": "Drew Barrymore"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Mel Gibson's sidekick in the 'Lethal Weapon' films?",
        "Answer": "Danny Glover"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian played the leading role in the TV series 'Sorry'?",
        "Answer": "Ronnie Corbett"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "By what stage name were the double act of Edward McGuinness and Cyril Mead better known, who had there own BBC TV show from 1978 to 1991?",
        "Answer": "Little And Large"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the cartoon character that chases after Roadrunner?",
        "Answer": "Wile E. Coyote"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1970 film directed by Robert Altman, was later turned into a TV series?",
        "Answer": "'MASH'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical film was the first to include the word 'bloody'?",
        "Answer": "'My Fair Lady'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what American state does most of the movie 'White Christmas' take place?",
        "Answer": "Vermont"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which star or 'The Goodies' also starred in 'The Bubblegum Brigade'?",
        "Answer": "Bill Oddie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Matrix', by what name is Keanu Reeve's character Thomas A. Anderson commonly known?",
        "Answer": "Neo"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British actress played Ophelia in the 1996 film 'Hamlet'?",
        "Answer": "Kate Winslet"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor has appeared in the films 'Mrs Doubtfire', 'The Lawnmower Man' and 'Mars Attacks'?",
        "Answer": "Pierce Brosnan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which three different actors played Batman in the movies between 1989 and 1997?",
        "Answer": "Michael Keaton, Val Kilmer and George Clooney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1933 film is set on and around Skull Island?",
        "Answer": "'King Kong'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What American film was released in France with a title which translated as 'Life, Love, Cows'?",
        "Answer": "City Slickers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the title of a famous film, how is Uncas Chingacgook better known?",
        "Answer": "The Last Of The Mohicans"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What character was Henry Winkler best known for playing?",
        "Answer": "Fonzie (in 'Happy Days')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the first character to speak in the film 'Star Wars'?",
        "Answer": "C3P0"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous film director directed the second segment of the 1983 film 'Twighlight Zone: The Movie'?",
        "Answer": "Steven Spielberg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1967 film starred Sidney Poiter, and had a theme tune performed by Lulu?",
        "Answer": "'To Sir With Love'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1995 film is the main character called Jim Lovell?",
        "Answer": "Apollo 13"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the films 'Faster, Pussycat! Kill! Kill!' and 'Beyond The Valley Of The Dolls'?",
        "Answer": "Russ Meyer"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show, what kind of animal was 'Gentle Ben'?",
        "Answer": "A bear"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the sorceror in the Disney film 'Fantasia'?",
        "Answer": "Yensid (Disney spelt backwards)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What three colours made up Krystof Kieslowski's 'Three Colours' trilogy of films?",
        "Answer": "Blue, White and Red."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On TV what is the real name of the 'Naked Chef'?",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 1997 Spanish film 'Open Your Eyes' was remade into which American film starring Tom Cruise?",
        "Answer": "'Vanilla Sky'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Al Pacino portray '60 minutes' producer Lowell Bergman?",
        "Answer": "'The Insider'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Mel Gibson play a character who was frozen for 50 years?",
        "Answer": "'Forever Young'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress was nominated for a best actress Oscar for her performance in the 1995 film 'Casino'?",
        "Answer": "Sharon Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which musical duo wrote the lyrics and music for the film 'The Sound Of Music'?",
        "Answer": "Rogers and Hammerstein"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1933, what became the only film to have it's sequel released in the same year?",
        "Answer": "King Kong (the sequel was called 'The Son of Kong')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character did Christopher Ryan play in the TV comedy series 'The Young Ones'?",
        "Answer": "Mike"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Around which war is 'The Dirty Dozen' set?",
        "Answer": "World War 2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Who Framed Roger Rabbit', what is the first name of Roger's wife?",
        "Answer": "Jessica"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor starred in 'Snake Eyes', 'Peggy Sue Got Married' and 'Moonstruck'?",
        "Answer": "Nicolas Cage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Audrey Hepburn's character in the 1964 film 'My Fair Lady'?",
        "Answer": "Eliza Doolittle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What colour is Noddy's hat?",
        "Answer": "Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1974 film 'The Conversation'? Francis Ford Coppola, Martin Scorcese or Stanley Kubrick?",
        "Answer": "Francis Ford Coppola"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film starring Julia Roberts had a working title of '$3,000'?",
        "Answer": "'Pretty Woman'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Frank Spencer's wife's name in the TV comedy show 'Some Mothers Do Have 'Em'?",
        "Answer": "Betty"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the screen name of actor Lee Yuen Kim?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Lee"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "During the making of which film did Brad Pitt chip his tooth, but refuse to have it capped as he felt it added to his character?",
        "Answer": "Fight Club"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1992 film had the tag line 'A brutal murder. A brilliant killer. A cop who can't resist the danger.'?",
        "Answer": "Basic Instinct"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Grange Hill how did Danny Kendall die?",
        "Answer": "Of a brain haemmorrhage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the Green Goblin in the 2002 film 'Spider-Man'?",
        "Answer": "Willem Dafoe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1991 film stars Billy Crystal as a man plagued by mid-life crisis who goes on a cattle driving vacation?",
        "Answer": "'City Slickers'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film was a biography of singer-comedienne Fanny Brice and who played the leading role?",
        "Answer": "'Funny Girl', Barbra Streisand."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV show featured a dog called 'Freeway'?",
        "Answer": "'Hart To Hart'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How old was Shirley Temple when she made her last film in 1949? 21, 31 or 41?",
        "Answer": "21"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the title role in the TV series 'A Touch Of Frost'?",
        "Answer": "David Jason"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The line 'I can't feel anything but gratitude for every single moment of my stupid little life' comes from which Oscar winning film?",
        "Answer": "'American Beauty'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV character named his son Mearth?",
        "Answer": "Mork (from 'Mork and Mindy')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Actress Kate Hudson is the daughter of which other actress?",
        "Answer": "Goldie Hawn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Citizen Kane', what is dying word of Charles Foster Kane, which a reporter tries to investigate the significance of?",
        "Answer": "Rosebud"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 1998 version of 'The Parent Trap', the meddlesome twin sisters were both played by Lindsay Lohan. Who played them in the classic Walt Disney original?",
        "Answer": "Hayley Mills"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1971 film 'The French Connection'? William Friedkin, Peter Weir or John Schlesinger?",
        "Answer": "William Friedkin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which country is also the title of a 1985 film by Terry Gilliam?",
        "Answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of the last film in the 'Omen' trilogy featuring the character of Damian?",
        "Answer": "'The Final Conflict'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played opposite Ewan McGregor as Nick Leeson's wife in the film 'Rogue Trader'?",
        "Answer": "Anna Friel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who did actor David Arquette marry in 1999?",
        "Answer": "Courtney Cox"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of Steven Spielberg's first full length movie? 'Barricade', 'Duel' or 'Nineteen Forty-One'?",
        "Answer": "Duel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which film does the line 'Louis, I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship' come?",
        "Answer": "'Casablanca'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose first spoken words on screen were 'Hot Dogs' in 1929?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first female to present of Points of View on a regular basis?",
        "Answer": "Anne Robinson"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1991 film 'JFK'?",
        "Answer": "Oliver Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the TV series 'Dr Who', how many hearts does a Time Lord have?",
        "Answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the first vocalist to actually appear in the credits sequence of a James Bond film?",
        "Answer": "Sheena Easton (in 'For Your Eyes Only')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what year did film star James Dean die? 1955, 1959 or 1964?",
        "Answer": "1955"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress won a lifetime acheivement award at the Cannes Film Festival in 2001?",
        "Answer": "Melanie Griffith"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following did not star in the 1972 film 'Deliverance'? Ned Beatty, Peter Coyote or Jon Voight?",
        "Answer": "Peter Coyote"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What subject was Rodney studying in 'Only Fools And Horses'?",
        "Answer": "Computing"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "According to the film 'It's A Wonderful Life' how do you know when an angel has got his wings?",
        "Answer": "A bell rings"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who captained the submarine in Stingray?",
        "Answer": "Troy Tempest"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who were the first animated television couple to sleep in a double bed?",
        "Answer": "Fred and Wilma Flintstone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Lois Lane in the 1978 film 'Superman'?",
        "Answer": "Margot Kidder"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous comedian and writer had a UK TV series in the 1990s called 'The Man From Auntie'?",
        "Answer": "Ben Elton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played a detective in the 1968 film 'The Thomas Crown Affair' and played a psychologist in the 1999 remake?",
        "Answer": "Faye Dunaway"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Jodie Foster, Mel Brooks and Cindy Crawford have all lended their voices to phone callers on what TV sitcom?",
        "Answer": "'Frasier'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'The Simpsons', who was kicked out of the group the Be-Sharpes and replaced by Barney?",
        "Answer": "Police Chief Clancy Wiggum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is Truman's surname in the film 'The Truman Show'?",
        "Answer": "Burbank"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What relation is Supergirl to Superman?",
        "Answer": "Cousin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The first ever film was shown in 1895 in which country?",
        "Answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer provides the voice for Chef in South Park?",
        "Answer": "Isaac Hayes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV show 'The Young Ones', what were the first names of the four main characters?",
        "Answer": "Rick, Neil, Mike and Vyvian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Blink 182 get there name from the number of times Al Pacino uses the 'f word' in which film?",
        "Answer": "Scarface"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the quizmaster on the TV show 'Fifteen to One'?",
        "Answer": "William G Stewart"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the title of New Order's 1990 hit with the England football squad?",
        "Answer": "'World In Motion'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What nationality was the actor Errol Flynn?",
        "Answer": "Australian"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Crocodile Dundee's real first name?",
        "Answer": "Mick (or Michael)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Martin Sheen had a heart-attack during the filming of which 1979 film?",
        "Answer": "Apocalypse Now"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Batman in the 1997 film 'Batman and Robin'?",
        "Answer": "George Clooney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous person in history did Mel Gibson play in the film 'Braveheart'?",
        "Answer": "William Wallace"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Basil Rathbone was famous for playing which character in a series of 1940's films?",
        "Answer": "Sherlock Holmes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Natural Born Killers'?",
        "Answer": "Oliver Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the Simpsons, what are the names of Marge's two sisters?",
        "Answer": "Patty and Selma"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character was 'the fastest mouse in all Mehico'?",
        "Answer": "Speedy Gonzales"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the horse in the film 'Toy Story 2'?",
        "Answer": "Bullseye"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For what film were the best actress and supporting actress Oscars awarded in 1994?",
        "Answer": "The Piano"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the tiger in the film 'The Jungle Book'?",
        "Answer": "Shere Khan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1980 film featured the character of 'Ming The Merciless'?",
        "Answer": "'Flash Gordon'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did Al Pacino play the character of Tony Montana?",
        "Answer": "'Scarface'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In October 2002, it was announced that which Big Brother 3 star was to join the cast of the musical 'Boogie Nights'?",
        "Answer": "Jonny"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following Bond films had a theme tune which was not sung by a female? Licence To Kill, From Russia With Love or Octopussy?",
        "Answer": "From Russia With Love"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which silent film star was known as America's Sweetheart?",
        "Answer": "Mary Pickford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What yearly political event was broadcast live on British TV for the first time in March 1990?",
        "Answer": "The Budget"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Mrs Robinson in the film 'The Graduate'?",
        "Answer": "Anne Bancroft"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 2002 film 'Death Watch' was centred around which war?",
        "Answer": "World War I"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "John Wayne won an Oscar for his performance in what 1969 film, which was based on a novel by Charles Portis?",
        "Answer": "'True Grit'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "At which film festival is the Palm d'Or awarded?",
        "Answer": "Cannes"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played a mermaid in the film 'Splash'?",
        "Answer": "Daryl Hannah"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What type of dog is Ren in 'The Ren and Stimpy Show'?",
        "Answer": "Chihuahua"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'Dr Who' what was the name of the character who created the Daleks?",
        "Answer": "Davros"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What won 'Best TV Comedy' at the British Comedy Awards in 2002? 'The Office', 'Phoenix Nights' or 'Eastenders'?",
        "Answer": "The Office"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film did the character of Marion Crane famously die?",
        "Answer": "'Psycho'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film does the main character befriend a dog he calls 'two socks'?",
        "Answer": "Dances With Wolves"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was Dr Richard Kimble accused of killing in the 'The Fugitive'?",
        "Answer": "His Wife"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the detective 'Columbo' on TV?",
        "Answer": "Peter Falk"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which year were Oscars first awarded for supporting actors and actresses? 1936, 1956 or 1976?",
        "Answer": "1936"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What fairytale has been filmed the most?",
        "Answer": "'Cinderalla'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The Disney character Oswald The Lucky Rabbit was modified in 1928 to become who?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Mouse"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which 2 films was Marlon Brando awarded Oscars?",
        "Answer": "On the Waterfront, The Godfather"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Eliza Doolittle in the film 'My Fair Lady'?",
        "Answer": "Audrey Hepburn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is name of the main female character, played by Carrie-Anne Moss in the film 'The Matrix'?",
        "Answer": "Trinity"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 2002, which film won Oscars for Best Sound and Best Editing?",
        "Answer": "Black Hawk Down"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1967 film would you find the character of Detective Virgil Tibbs?",
        "Answer": "In The Heat Of The Night"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many films did Marilyn Monroe make? 7, 15 or 30?",
        "Answer": "30"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV police series began as a one off programme called 'Woodentop'?",
        "Answer": "'The Bill'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of first feature film in which the dog 'Lassie' appeared?",
        "Answer": "'Lassie Come Home'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Dustin Hoffman's first major role was in what 1967 film?",
        "Answer": "'The Graduate'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What animal does Tramp get to remove Lady's muzzle in the film 'Lady and the Tramp'?",
        "Answer": "Beaver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1986 film is based on a story by Stephen King called 'The Body'?",
        "Answer": "'Stand By Me'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Luke Skywalker in the film 'Star Wars'?",
        "Answer": "Mark Hamill"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1997 film starred John Travolta as an angel?",
        "Answer": "'Michael'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "How many buttons did Popeye have on his jacket?",
        "Answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In Tim Burton's fame 'The Planet Of The Apes' who played the character which was played by Charlton Heston in the original?",
        "Answer": "Mark Wahlberg"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor won an oscar for playing Vito Corleone in 'The Godfather Part II'?",
        "Answer": "Robert De Niro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress did Freddie Prince Jnr marry in September 2002?",
        "Answer": "Sarah Michelle Gellar"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cat was the most popular cartoon character before Mickey Mouse?",
        "Answer": "Felix The Cat"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the President in the film 'Air Force One'?",
        "Answer": "Harrison Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What were the full titles of the two 'Bill and Ted' movies?",
        "Answer": "'Bill and Ted's Excellent Adventure' and 'Bill and Ted's Bogus Journey'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American TV sitcom has a theme tune called 'Thank You For Being A Friend'?",
        "Answer": "'The Golden Girls'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the donkey in the film 'Shrek'?",
        "Answer": "Donkey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Bambi', what is the name of Bambi's rabbit friend?",
        "Answer": "Thumper"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which boxer did Robert De Niro play in the film 'Raging Bull'?",
        "Answer": "Jake La Motta"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1952 film 'The Quiet Man'? David Lean, John Ford or Fedrico Fellini?",
        "Answer": "John Ford"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the following actors did not appear in the film 'Platoon'? Johnny Depp, River Phoenix or Tom Berenger?",
        "Answer": "River Phoenix"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Pebbles and Bam Bam' was a spin-off of which TV series?",
        "Answer": "'The Flintstones'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the song which won an Oscar for the film 'an officer and a gentleman'?",
        "Answer": "'Up where we belong'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress won an Oscar for the 1990 film 'Ghost'?",
        "Answer": "Whoopi Golberg (for best supporting actress)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which film does the line 'If Mr. McMurphy doesn't want to take his medication orally, I'm sure we can arrange that he can have it some other way' come?",
        "Answer": "'One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the musical 'Annie', what is orphan Annie's dog called?",
        "Answer": "Sandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film star had his feet insured for one hundred and fifty thousand dollars?",
        "Answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "For which two films has Michael Caine won best supporting actor Oscars?",
        "Answer": "'Hannah And Her Sisters' and 'Cider House Rules'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which TV series might you have found the 'Pacific Princess'?",
        "Answer": "'Love Boat'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of the rabbit in the Magic Roundabout?",
        "Answer": "Dylan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the profession of the main character in the 2001 film 'The Man Who Wasn't There'?",
        "Answer": "Barber"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actress once said 'I've been in more laps than a napkin'?",
        "Answer": "Mae West"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "True or False: The first Mickey Mouse movie was silent?",
        "Answer": "True (it was called 'Plane Crazy')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who was the male lead who starred with Demi Moore in the film 'Ghost'?",
        "Answer": "Patrick Swayze"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The characters Bert and Ernie from Sesame street were named after a policeman and taxi driver from what famous film?",
        "Answer": "'It's A Wonderful Life'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "James Cagney is often misquoted by impressionists as saying 'You dirty rat'. What was his exact original words that led to this misquote?",
        "Answer": "'You dirty double-crossing rat'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What's the names of Donald Duck's three nephews?",
        "Answer": "Huey, Dewey and Louie."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous TV comedian changed his name from Eric Bartholomew?",
        "Answer": "Eric Morecambe"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the cowboy in the film 'Toy Story'?",
        "Answer": "Woody"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which city is the 2001 film 'Mulholland Drive' set?",
        "Answer": "Los Angeles"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The 1956 film 'Forbidden Planet' is loosely based on which Shakespeare play?",
        "Answer": "'The Tempest'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What feature did German film director Fritz Lang include for the first time in the film 'The Woman in the Moon' which has today become a standard part of space-launch protocol?",
        "Answer": "The backward countdown"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Dr Jekyll in the 1996 film 'Mary Reilly'?",
        "Answer": "John Malkovich"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "'Restyle Perm' is an anagram of which famous actress?",
        "Answer": "Meryl Streep"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon cat would you associate with the bird Tweety Pie?",
        "Answer": "Sylvester"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Samantha in the TV series 'Sex And The City'?",
        "Answer": "Kim Cattrall"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What actor played 'Crocodile Dundee'?",
        "Answer": "Paul Hogan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Tim Burton film starred Alec Baldwin and Geena Davis?",
        "Answer": "Beetlejuice"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the Oscar-winning film 'The English Patient'?",
        "Answer": "Anthony Minghella"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the Honey Rider in an early James Bond film?",
        "Answer": "Ursula Andress (in 'Dr No')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the 'Dukes Of Hazzard' was General Lee a car, a dog, or a person?",
        "Answer": "A car"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which two actors played Hamlet in the 1990 and 1996 films, both called 'Hamlet'?",
        "Answer": "Mel Gibson (1990) and Kenneth Branagh (1996)."
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film starring Arnold Swarzenegger, was based on a short story called 'We Can Remember It For You Wholesale'?",
        "Answer": "'Total Recall'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Cut-throat Jake was the arch enemy of who?",
        "Answer": "Captain Pugwash"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred opposite Michael Douglas in the 1984 film 'Romancing The Stone'?",
        "Answer": "Kathleen Turner"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1933 film did Fay Wray star as Ann Darrow?",
        "Answer": "King Kong"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Hercule Poirot in the films 'Death On The Nile' and 'Appointment With Death'?",
        "Answer": "Peter Ustinov"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who or what was Herbie in the 1974 film 'Herbie Rides Again'?",
        "Answer": "A car (Volkswagen Beetle)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which name does Paul O'Grady usually use when appearing on TV?",
        "Answer": "Lily Savage"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV puppet had an arch enemy called Grotbags?",
        "Answer": "Emu"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which country was the 1999 film 'Human Traffic' set?",
        "Answer": "Wales"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV show introduced Bonnie Langford, Bobby Crush and Lena Zavaroni?",
        "Answer": "'Opportunity Knocks'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the title role in the 2002 film 'Spiderman'?",
        "Answer": "Tobey Maguire"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress appeared in the films 'Get Shorty', 'Ruthless People' and 'The First Wives Club'?",
        "Answer": "Bette Midler"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays Dr. Evil in the 'Austin Powers' films?",
        "Answer": "Mike Myers"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which comedian's real name is Robert Davies?",
        "Answer": "Jasper Carrot"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Whose was the first star to be placed on the Hollywood Walk Of Fame?",
        "Answer": "Joanne Woodward"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Name the 2 stars of 'The Sweeny'?",
        "Answer": "John Thaw and Dennis Waterman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Psycho' what is Norman Bates' hobby?",
        "Answer": "Taxidermy (stuffing birds)"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What American film was released in France with a title which translated as 'Life, Love, Cows'?",
        "Answer": "'City Slickers'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Monty Python star won a lifetime acheivement award at the British Comedy Awards in 2002?",
        "Answer": "Michael Palin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which line in Casablanca was famously mis-translated into German as 'I look in your eyes, little one.'?",
        "Answer": "'Here's looking at you, kid'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "From which 1999 film do the lines 'I feel like I've been in a coma for the past twenty years. And I'm just now waking up.' come?",
        "Answer": "'American Beauty'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the TV series 'The Simpsons', who replaced Sideshow Bob?",
        "Answer": "Sideshow Mel"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the film 'Full Metal Jacket'?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actress provided the voice of Maggie in the TV show The Simpsons when she uttered her first word?",
        "Answer": "Elizabeth Taylor"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which TV comedian plays the character of Alan Partridge?",
        "Answer": "Steve Coogan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Stanley Kubrick film was based on a short story by Gustav Hasford called 'The Short Timers'?",
        "Answer": "'Full Metal Jacket'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British actress has appeared in the films 'The Last Days Of Disco', 'Serendipity' and 'Pearl Harbour'?",
        "Answer": "Kate Beckinsale"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what American TV series did David Duchovny appear as transvestite Dennis/Denise Bryson?",
        "Answer": "Twin Peaks"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played 'Balowski' in the TV comedy series 'The Young Ones'?",
        "Answer": "Alexie Sayle"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1989 film 'Crimes And Misdemeanors'? Warren Beatty, Woody Allen or Robert Redford?",
        "Answer": "Woody Allen"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1982 stars Dustin Hoffman as an actor who disguises himself as a woman to get work?",
        "Answer": "'Tootsie'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress played the female lead in the film 'Out Of Africa'?",
        "Answer": "Meryl Streep"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which long-running show was first broadcast in 1958 when it was presented by a former Miss Great Britain and an ex-Army Officer?",
        "Answer": "Blue Peter"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Bert and Ernie from 'Sesame Street' are named after characters in what classic film?",
        "Answer": "It's A Wonderful Life"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the first in Krzysztof Kieslowski's 'Three Colours' trilogy of films called?",
        "Answer": "Three Colours: Blue"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who plays the role of Sharon Watts in the TV soap opera 'Eastenders'?",
        "Answer": "Letitia Dean"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What would the highest possible score be on the TV quiz show 'Fifteen To One'?",
        "Answer": "433"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which member of the Monty Python team was a doctor?",
        "Answer": "Graham Chapman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the Lone Ranger's horse called?",
        "Answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film star has the real name of Chan Kongsang?",
        "Answer": "Jackie Chan"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the first cartoon created for use with a soundtrack?",
        "Answer": "Steamboat Willie"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which character has been played on screen by Tyrone Power and Alain Denoin?",
        "Answer": "Zorro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which film, directed by Terry Gilliam and starring Bruce Willis, was based on the short French film, 'La Jetee'?",
        "Answer": "'Twelve Monkeys'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the Riddler in the 1995 film 'Batman Forever'?",
        "Answer": "Jim Carrey"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What is the name of The Jetsons' dog? Astro, Apollo or Maris?",
        "Answer": "Astro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 'J' is Homer Simpson's middle name?",
        "Answer": "Jay"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Dr Grant in the film 'Jurassic Park'?",
        "Answer": "Sam Neill"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What silent film star had a contract which forbid him from smiling on screen?",
        "Answer": "Buster Keaton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mel Gibson, Whoopi Goldberg and R.E.M. have all made guest appearances on which children's TV show?",
        "Answer": "'Sesame Street'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1995 film featured the characters of Mr Potato Head, Bo Peep and Slinky Dog?",
        "Answer": "'Toy Story'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played a singer called Rachel Marron in a 1992 fillm?",
        "Answer": "Whitney Houston (in 'The Bodyguard')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1962 film is based on the novel 'The Executioners' by John D. MacDonald?",
        "Answer": "'Cape Fear'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What kind of animal is Pingu?",
        "Answer": "Penguin"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In July 2002, actress Angelina Jolie filed for divorce from which actor?",
        "Answer": "Billy Bob Thornton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "David Prowse is best known for playing what Star Wars character?",
        "Answer": "Darth Vader"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cult TV show featured the characters called Donna Hayward, Doctor Jacobi and the Log Lady?",
        "Answer": "'Twin Peaks'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which cartoon character lived at 52 Festive Road, London?",
        "Answer": "Mr Benn"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the third fillm in the 'Die Hard' series?",
        "Answer": "'Die Hard: With A Vengeance"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In 1990, who became the oldest recipient of a best actress Oscar?",
        "Answer": "Jessica Tandy"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor played the leading role in Alfred Hitchcock's 'North by north-west'?",
        "Answer": "Cary Grant"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of Rodney's wife in 'Only Fools And Horses'?",
        "Answer": "Cassandra"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was Oliver Reed's last film?",
        "Answer": "'Gladiator'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 'V. V.' is John TravoltaÃÂ¢Ã¢âÂ¬Ã¢âÂ¢s character's name in the film 'Pulp Fiction'?",
        "Answer": "Vince Vega"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which American actress played Carrie in 'Four Weddings and a Funeral'?",
        "Answer": "Andie MacDowell"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who starred as Mary Poppins in the 1964 film of the same name?",
        "Answer": "Julie Andrews"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In what 1971 film did Roy Kinnear play Mr Salt?",
        "Answer": "'Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "On which TV comedy show might you find the characters of Jesse, Bob Fleming and Competitive Dad?",
        "Answer": "'The Fast Show'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which 1993 film is the main character called Phil Connors?",
        "Answer": "Groundhog Day"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actress starred in 'The Pelican Brief' and 'Sleeping With The Enemy'?",
        "Answer": "Julia Roberts"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'The Life Of Brian', who played Biggus Dickus?",
        "Answer": "Graham Chapman"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What does the letter 'T' stand for in the Star Trek character James T. Kirk's name?",
        "Answer": "Tiberius"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which Monty Python star once played an art critic in 'Doctor Who'?",
        "Answer": "John Cleese"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who is the patron saint of television?",
        "Answer": "Saint Clare"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Mickey Mouse is named after which actor?",
        "Answer": "Mickey Rooney"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Robert Englund is best known for playing which character in a series of horror films?",
        "Answer": "Freddy Krueger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the movie '2001: A Space Odysey, what was the computer's name?",
        "Answer": "HAL"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played Al Capone in the 1987 film 'The Untouchables'?",
        "Answer": "Robert De Niro"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1987 film received 9 nominations at the Oscars in 1988?",
        "Answer": "'The Last Emperor'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which British actor plays Thomas Fowler in the 2002 film 'The Quiet American'?",
        "Answer": "Michael Caine"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Adapted from a British TV series, what 1997 featured Val Kilmer in the leading role?",
        "Answer": "'The Saint'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who directed the 1956 film 'The Killing'? Roman Polanski, Stanley Kubrick or Francis Ford Copolla?",
        "Answer": "Stanley Kubrick"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In which film would you first have come across the character of Marty McFly?",
        "Answer": "Back To The Future"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was the name of the character in 'Wacky Races' who drove 'the Turbo Terrific'?",
        "Answer": "Peter Perfect"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Who played the psychopath Max Cady in the 1991 version of 'Cape Fear' and who played him in the 1962 version?",
        "Answer": "Robert De Niro and Robert Michum"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which of the characters in the 'Wizard of Oz' would most accurately fit the description of 'Vacuous'? The Scarecrow, Tin Man or Lion?",
        "Answer": "Scarecrow"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "The character played by Halle Berry in the 1994 film 'The Flintstones' shares her name with what famous actress?",
        "Answer": "Sharon Stone"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which actor and actress play the two main characters Walter and Nadia in the film 'Blind Date'?",
        "Answer": "Bruce Willis and Kim Basinger"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "More widely recognised as an actor, who won the 1997 Oscar for best adapted screenplay for the film 'Slingblade'?",
        "Answer": "Billy Bob Thornton"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What product did Linda Bellingham advertise on TV for 12 years?",
        "Answer": "OXO"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which 1975 film became only the second to win all five major Oscars - Best Picture, Best Director, Best Actor, Best Actress and Best Screenplay?",
        "Answer": "'One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What was ITVs first twice weekly soap opera?",
        "Answer": "Emergency Ward 10"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the film 'Casablanca', how many times does Humphrey Bogart say 'Play it again Sam'?",
        "Answer": "Never"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "In the cartoon series 'Wacky Races', which two characters drove the 'mean machine'?",
        "Answer": "Dick Dastardly and Muttley"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which singer won the best actress award at the 2000 Cannes Film Festival?",
        "Answer": "Bjork (for 'Dancer In The Dark')"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "What 1969 James Bond is the longest at 140 minutes?",
        "Answer": "'On Her Majesty's Secret Service'"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Sigourney Weaver's film debut was a non-speaking role in which Woody Allen film?",
        "Answer": "Annie Hall"
    },
    {
        "Quiz question": "Which famous actor had his scenes cut from the 1983 film 'The Big Chill'",
        "Answer": "Kevin Costner"
    }
]